<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<?metadataRepository version='1.1.0'?>
<repository name='Update Site' type='org.eclipse.equinox.internal.p2.metadata.repository.LocalMetadataRepository' version='1.0.0'>
  <properties size='2'>
    <property name='p2.timestamp' value='1538569766514'/>
    <property name='p2.compressed' value='false'/>
  </properties>
  <units size='7'>
    <unit id='cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.feature.group' version='0.2.2' singleton='false'>
      <update id='cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.feature.group' range='[0.0.0,0.2.2)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='4'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='cleonproject.deliverables.release_1'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='No description available'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description.url' value='http://www.zwyssig.info/description'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.type.group' value='true'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='1'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.feature.group' version='0.2.2'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='30'>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='ch.actifsource.core' range='9.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='ch.actifsource.environment' range='9.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='ch.actifsource.util' range='9.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='ch.actifsource.generator' range='9.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='ch.actifsource.ui.wizard.generic' range='9.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='ch.actifsource.ui.wizard' range='9.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='ch.actifsource.xml' range='9.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.support.collaboration.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.support.documentation.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.deployment.chocolatey.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.common.knowledge.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.implementation.gradle.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.conception.organisation.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.implementation.plantuml.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.conception.applications.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.conception.testing.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.conception.architecture.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.common.glossary.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.initialization.projectmanagement.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.common.analysis.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.common.doc.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.common.resources.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.common.xml.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.initialization.processlanguage.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.common.importwizard.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.conception.platform.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.conception.network.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.conception.actifsource.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.model.project.builtin' range='[0.2.2,0.2.2]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.feature.jar' range='[0.2.2,0.2.2]'>
          <filter>
            (org.eclipse.update.install.features=true)
          </filter>
        </required>
      </requires>
      <touchpoint id='null' version='0.0.0'/>
      <licenses size='1'>
        <license uri='http://www.zwyssig.info/license' url='http://www.zwyssig.info/license'>
          cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 Software License Agreement&#xA;NOTICE TO USER: PLEASE READ THIS AGREEMENT CAREFULLY. BY COPYING,&#xA;INSTALLING OR USING ALL OR ANY PORTION OF THE SOFTWARE YOU ACCEPT&#xA;ALL THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS AGREEMENT, INCLUDING, IN&#xA;PARTICULAR THE PROVISIONS ON: TRANSFERABILITY IN SECTION 4; WARRANTY&#xA;IN SECTIONS 6 AND 7; LIABILITY IN SECTION 8; CONNECTIVITY AND&#xA;PRIVACY IN SECTION 13; AND SPECIFIC PROVISIONS AND EXCEPTIONS&#xA;IN SECTION 14. YOU AGREE THAT THIS AGREEMENT IS LIKE ANY WRITTEN&#xA;NEGOTIATED AGREEMENT SIGNED BY YOU. THIS AGREEMENT IS ENFORCEABLE&#xA;AGAINST YOU AND ANY LEGAL ENTITY THAT OBTAINED THE SOFTWARE AND&#xA;ON WHOSE BEHALF IT IS USED: FOR EXAMPLE, IF APPLICABLE, YOUR&#xA;EMPLOYER. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS AGREEMENT,&#xA;DO NOT USE AND/OR BUY THE SOFTWARE.&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 AND ITS SUPPLIERS OWN ALL INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY IN&#xA;THE SOFTWARE. THE SOFTWARE IS LICENSED, NOT SOLD. cleonproject.deliverables.release_1&#xA;PERMITS YOU TO COPY, DOWNLOAD, INSTALL, USE, OR OTHERWISE BENEFIT&#xA;FROM THE FUNCTIONALITY OR INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY OF THE SOFTWARE&#xA;ONLY IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS AGREEMENT. USE OF SOME&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 AND SOME THIRD PARTY MATERIALS AND SERVICES INCLUDED&#xA;IN OR ACCESSED THROUGH THE SOFTWARE MAY BE SUBJECT TO OTHER TERMS&#xA;AND CONDITIONS TYPICALLY FOUND IN A SEPARATE LICENSE AGREEMENT,&#xA;TERMS OF USE OR “READ ME” FILE LOCATED WITHIN OR NEAR SUCH MATERIALS&#xA;AND SERVICES OR AT http://www.zwyssig.info.&#xA;THE SOFTWARE MAY CAUSE YOUR COMPUTER TO AUTOMATICALLY CONNECT&#xA;TO THE INTERNET. SEE SECTIONS 13 AND 14 FOR ADDITIONAL INFORMATION.&#xA;THE SOFTWARE MAY INCLUDE PRODUCT ACTIVATION AND OTHER TECHNOLOGY&#xA;DESIGNED TO PREVENT UNAUTHORIZED USE AND COPYING. THIS TECHNOLOGY&#xA;MAY CAUSE YOUR COMPUTER TO AUTOMATICALLY CONNECT TO THE INTERNET&#xA;AS DESCRIBED IN SECTION 13. ADDITIONALLY, ONCE CONNECTED, THE&#xA;SOFTWARE MAY TRANSMIT YOUR SERIAL NUMBER TO cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 AND IN&#xA;DOING SO MAY PREVENT USES OF THE SOFTWARE THAT ARE NOT PERMITTED.&#xA;VISIT http://www.cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.com FOR ADDITIONAL INFORMATION ABOUT&#xA;PRODUCT ACTIVATION.&#xA;1. Definitions.&#xA;“cleonproject.deliverables.release_1” means Zwyssig Informatik GmbH, &#xA;Switzerland.&#xA;“Computer” means a virtual or physical computer device that accepts&#xA;information in digital or similar form and manipulates it for&#xA;a specific result based on a sequence of instructions.&#xA;“Internal Network” means a private, proprietary network resource&#xA;accessible only by employees and individual contractors (i.e.,&#xA;temporary employees) of a specific corporation or similar business&#xA;entity. Internal Network does not include portions of the Internet&#xA;or any other network community open to the public, such as membership&#xA;or subscription driven groups, associations and similar organizations.&#xA;“Output File” means an output file you create with the Software.&#xA;“Permitted Number” means one (1) unless otherwise indicated under&#xA;a valid license (e.g., volume license) granted by cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.&#xA;“Software” means (a) all of the information with which this agreement&#xA;is provided, including but not limited to (i) cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 or&#xA;third party software files and other computer information; (ii)&#xA;sample files bundled with cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 software or obtained from&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 through a separate service; (iii) related explanatory&#xA;written materials and files (“Documentation”); and (b) any modified&#xA;versions and copies of, and upgrades, updates and additions to,&#xA;such information, provided to you by cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 at any time,&#xA;to the extent not provided under a separate agreement (collectively,&#xA;“Updates”).&#xA;2. Software License.&#xA;If you obtained the Software and any required serial number(s)&#xA;from cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 or one of its authorized licensees and as long&#xA;as you comply with the terms of this agreement, cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 grants&#xA;you a non-exclusive license to install and use the Software in&#xA;a manner consistent with its design and Documentation and as&#xA;further set forth below. See Section 14 for specific provisions&#xA;related to the use of certain products and components.&#xA;2.1 General Use. You may install and use one copy of the Software&#xA;on up to the Permitted Number of your compatible Computers as&#xA;long as, when required by the Software, you present a valid serial&#xA;number for each copy; and&#xA;2.2 Distribution from Server. You may copy an image of the Software&#xA;onto file server(s) within your Internal Network for the purpose&#xA;of downloading and installing the Software onto Computers within&#xA;the same Internal Network for use as permitted by Section 2.1;&#xA;and&#xA;2.3 Server Use. You may install the Software on Computer file&#xA;server(s) within your Internal Network only for use of the Software&#xA;initiated by an individual from a Computer within the same Internal&#xA;Network as permitted by Section 2.1. The total number of users&#xA;(not the concurrent number of users) able to use the Software&#xA;on such Computer file server(s) may not exceed the Permitted&#xA;Number. By way of example, the foregoing does not permit you&#xA;to install or access (either directly or through commands, data&#xA;or instructions) the Software: (i) from or to a Computer not&#xA;part of your Internal Network, (ii) for enabling web hosted workgroups&#xA;or services available to the public, (iii) by any individual&#xA;or entity to use, download, copy or otherwise benefit from the&#xA;functionality of the Software unless licensed to do so by cleonproject.deliverables.release_1,&#xA;(iv) as a component of a system, workflow or service accessible&#xA;by more than the Permitted Number of users, or (v) for operations&#xA;not initiated by an individual user (e.g., automated server processing);&#xA;and&#xA;2.4 Backup Copy. You may make a reasonable number of backup copies&#xA;of the Software, provided your backup copies are not installed&#xA;or used for other than archival purposes.&#xA;2.5 Sample Application Code. You may modify the source code form&#xA;of those portions of such software programs that are identified&#xA;as sample code, sample application code, or components (each,&#xA;“Sample Application Code”) in the accompanying Documentation&#xA;solely for the purposes of designing, developing and testing&#xA;applications developed using cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 software programs; provided,&#xA;however, you are permitted to copy and distribute the Sample&#xA;Application Code (modified or unmodified) only if all of the&#xA;following conditions are met: (1) you distribute the compiled&#xA;object Sample Application Code with your application; (2) you&#xA;do not include the Sample Application Code in any product or&#xA;application designed for software development; and (3) you do&#xA;not use the cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 name, logos or other cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 trademarks&#xA;to market your application. You agree to indemnify, hold harmless&#xA;and defend cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 from and against any loss, damage, claims&#xA;or lawsuits, including attorney’s fees, that arise or result&#xA;from the use or distribution of your application. You may be&#xA;granted additional rights to modify or distribute cleonproject.deliverables.release_1&#xA;software code within documentation relating to such code and/or&#xA;the Software or in a separate agreement between you and cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.&#xA;2.6 Tryout Software. The Software, or portions of the Software,&#xA;may be configured to allow trial or tryout for a limited period&#xA;of time or for a limited number of launches. You are not permitted&#xA;to use the Software in a manner inconsistent with its design&#xA;or Documentation. For example, you may not use the Software after&#xA;its tryout period has ended unless you input a valid serial number.&#xA;ACCESS TO ANY OUTPUT FILES CREATED WITH THE SOFTWARE USED ON&#xA;A TRYOUT OR TRIAL BASIS IS ENTIRELY AT YOUR OWN RISK.&#xA;3. Intellectual Property Ownership.&#xA;The Software and any authorized copies that you make are the&#xA;intellectual property of and are owned by cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 and its&#xA;suppliers. The structure, organization and code of the Software&#xA;are the valuable trade secrets and confidential information of&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 and its suppliers. The Software is protected by law,&#xA;including but not limited to the copyright laws of the Switzerland&#xA;and other countries, and by international treaty provisions.&#xA;Except as expressly stated herein, this agreement does not grant&#xA;you any intellectual property rights in the Software and all&#xA;rights not expressly granted are reserved by cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 and&#xA;its suppliers.&#xA;4. Restrictions and Requirements.&#xA;4.1 Notices. Any permitted copy of the Software that you make&#xA;must contain the same copyright and other proprietary notices&#xA;that appear on or in the Software.&#xA;4.2 Use Obligations. You agree that you will not use the Software&#xA;other than as permitted by this agreement and that you will not&#xA;use the Software in a manner inconsistent with its design or&#xA;Documentation.&#xA;4.3 No Modifications. Except as permitted in Section 14, you&#xA;may not modify, adapt or translate the Software.&#xA;4.4 No Reverse Engineering. You will not reverse engineer, decompile,&#xA;disassemble or otherwise attempt to discover the source code&#xA;of the Software except to the extent you may be expressly permitted&#xA;under applicable law to decompile only in order to achieve interoperability&#xA;with the Software.&#xA;4.5 No Unbundling. The Software may include various applications,&#xA;utilities and components, may support multiple platforms and&#xA;languages and may be provided to you on multiple media or in&#xA;multiple copies. Nonetheless, the Software is designed and provided&#xA;to you as a single product to be used as a single product on&#xA;Computers as permitted by Sections 2 and 14. You are not required&#xA;to install all component parts of the Software, but you may not&#xA;unbundle the component parts of the Software for use on different&#xA;Computers. You may not unbundle or repackage the Software for&#xA;distribution, transfer or resale. See Section 14 for specific&#xA;exceptions to this Section 4.5.&#xA;4.6 No Transfer. YOU WILL NOT RENT, LEASE, SELL, SUBLICENSE,&#xA;ASSIGN OR TRANSFER YOUR RIGHTS IN THE SOFTWARE, OR AUTHORIZE&#xA;ANY PORTION OF THE SOFTWARE TO BE COPIED ONTO ANOTHER INDIVIDUAL&#xA;OR LEGAL ENTITY’S COMPUTER EXCEPT AS MAY BE EXPRESSLY PERMITTED&#xA;HEREIN. You may, however, permanently transfer all your rights&#xA;to use the Software to another individual or legal entity provided&#xA;that: (a) you also transfer (i) this agreement, (ii) the serial&#xA;number(s), the Software affixed to media provided by cleonproject.deliverables.release_1&#xA;or its authorized distributor, and all other software or hardware&#xA;bundled, packaged or pre-installed with the Software, including&#xA;all copies, upgrades, updates and prior versions, to such individual&#xA;or entity; (b) you retain no upgrades, updates or copies, including&#xA;backups and copies stored on a Computer; and (c) the receiving&#xA;party accepts the terms and conditions of this agreement and&#xA;any other terms and conditions under which you purchased a valid&#xA;license to the Software. NOTWITHSTANDING THE FOREGOING, YOU MAY&#xA;NOT TRANSFER EDUCATION, PRERELEASE,&#xA;OR NOT FOR RESALE COPIES OF THE SOFTWARE. Prior to a transfer&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 may require that you and the receiving party confirm&#xA;in writing your compliance with this agreement, provide cleonproject.deliverables.release_1&#xA;with information about yourselves, and register as end-users&#xA;of the Software. Allow 4-6 weeks to&#xA;transfer. Please visit http://www.cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.com or contact&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 for more information.&#xA;4.7 No Service Bureau. You will not use or offer the Software&#xA;on a service bureau basis. By way of example, you are not allowed&#xA;to offer the Software as a service (SaaS).&#xA;5. Updates.&#xA;If the Software is an upgrade or update to a previous version&#xA;of cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 software, you must possess a valid license to&#xA;such previous version in order to use such upgrade or update.&#xA;After you install such update or upgrade, you may continue to&#xA;use any such previous version in accordance with its end-user&#xA;license agreement only if (a) the upgrade or update and all previous&#xA;versions are installed on the same Computer, (b) the previous&#xA;versions or copies thereof are not transferred to another party&#xA;or device unless all copies of the update or upgrade are also&#xA;transferred to such party or device and (c) you acknowledge that&#xA;any obligation cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 may have to support the previous version(s)&#xA;may end upon the availability of the upgrade or update. No other&#xA;use of the previous version(s) is permitted after installation&#xA;of an update or upgrade. Upgrades and updates may be licensed&#xA;to you by cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 with additional or different terms.&#xA;6. LIMITED WARRANTY.&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 warrants to the individual or entity that first purchases&#xA;a license for the Software for use pursuant to the terms of this&#xA;agreement that the Software will perform substantially in accordance&#xA;with the Documentation for the ninety (90) day period following&#xA;receipt of the Software when used on the recommended operating&#xA;system and hardware configuration. Non-substantial variation&#xA;of performance from the Documentation does not establish a warranty&#xA;right. This limited warranty does not apply to the following,&#xA;which are made available AS-IS and without warranty from cleonproject.deliverables.release_1:&#xA;patches, pre-release (beta), trial, starter, evaluation, product&#xA;sampler, and not for resale (NFR) copies of the Software; websites,&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 Online Services; Third Party Online Services; and&#xA;any software made available by cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 for free via web download&#xA;from an cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 website. All warranty claims must be made,&#xA;along with proof of purchase, to cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 within such ninety&#xA;(90) day period. Visit the cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 website at http://www.cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.com&#xA;for more information about warranty claims. If the Software does&#xA;not perform substantially in accordance with the Documentation,&#xA;the entire liability of cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 and its affiliates and your&#xA;exclusive remedy will be limited to either, at cleonproject.deliverables.release_1’s&#xA;option, replacement of the Software or refund of the license&#xA;fee you paid for the Software. THE LIMITED WARRANTY SET FORTH&#xA;IN THIS SECTION GIVES YOU SPECIFIC LEGAL RIGHTS. YOU MAY HAVE&#xA;ADDITIONAL RIGHTS UNDER LAW WHICH VARY FROM JURISDICTION TO JURISDICTION.&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 DOES NOT SEEK TO LIMIT YOUR WARRANTY RIGHTS TO ANY&#xA;EXTENT NOT PERMITTED BY LAW. Please see Section 14 for jurisdiction-specific&#xA;provisions or contact cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.&#xA;7. DISCLAIMER.&#xA;THE FOREGOING LIMITED WARRANTY IS THE ONLY WARRANTY OFFERED BY&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 AND ITS AFFILIATES AND IT STATES THE SOLE AND EXCLUSIVE&#xA;REMEDIES FOR cleonproject.deliverables.release_1’S, ITS AFFILIATES’ OR SUPPLIERS’ BREACH&#xA;OF THAT OFFERED WARRANTY. THE FOREGOING OFFERED WARRANTY AND&#xA;ANY STATUTORY WARRANTY AND REMEDY THAT CANNOT BE EXCLUDED OR&#xA;LIMITED UNDER LAW ARE THE ONLY WARRANTIES APPLICABLE TO THE SOFTWARE.&#xA;OTHER THAN THOSE OFFERED AND STATUTORY WARRANTIES AND REMEDIES,&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.release_1, ITS AFFILIATES, SUPPLIERS AND CERTIFICATE AUTHORITIES&#xA;(DEFINED BELOW) DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES, CONDITIONS, REPRESENTATIONS&#xA;AND TERMS, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, WHETHER BY STATUTE, COMMON LAW,&#xA;CUSTOM, USAGE OR OTHERWISE AS TO ANY MATTER, INCLUDING BUT NOT&#xA;LIMITED TO PERFORMANCE, SECURITY, NON-INFRINGEMENT OF THIRD PARTY&#xA;RIGHTS, INTEGRATION, MERCHANTABILITY, QUIET ENJOYMENT, SATISFACTORY&#xA;QUALITY AND FITNESS FOR ANY PARTICULAR PURPOSE. OTHER THAN SUCH&#xA;OFFERED AND STATUTORY WARRANTIES AND REMEDIES, cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 AND&#xA;ITS SUPPLIERS PROVIDE THE SOFTWARE AND ACCESS TO ANY WEBSITES,&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 OR THIRD PARTY ONLINE SERVICES AND CERTIFICATE AUTHORITY&#xA;SERVICES AS-IS AND WITH ALL FAULTS. THIS DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTY&#xA;MAY NOT BE VALID IN SOME STATES. YOU MAY HAVE ADDITIONAL WARRANTY&#xA;RIGHTS UNDER LAW WHICH MAY NOT BE WAIVED OR DISCLAIMED. cleonproject.deliverables.release_1&#xA;DOES NOT SEEK TO LIMIT YOUR WARRANTY RIGHTS TO ANY EXTENT NOT&#xA;PERMITTED BY LAW. The provisions of Sections 7 and Section 8&#xA;will survive the termination of this agreement, howsoever caused,&#xA;but this will not imply or create any continued right to use&#xA;the Software after termination of this agreement.&#xA;8. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY.&#xA;EXCEPT FOR THE EXCLUSIVE REMEDY OFFERED BY cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 ABOVE&#xA;AND ANY REMEDIES THAT CANNOT BE EXCLUDED OR LIMITED UNDER LAW,&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.release_1, ITS AFFILIATES, SUPPLIERS, OR CERTIFICATE AUTHORITIES&#xA;WILL NOT BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR ANY LOSS, DAMAGES, CLAIMS OR COSTS&#xA;WHATSOEVER INCLUDING ANY CONSEQUENTIAL, INDIRECT OR INCIDENTAL&#xA;DAMAGES, ANY LOST PROFITS OR LOST SAVINGS, ANY DAMAGES RESULTING&#xA;FROM BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, PERSONAL INJURY OR FAILURE TO MEET&#xA;ANY DUTY OF CARE, OR CLAIMS BY A THIRD PARTY, EVEN IF AN cleonproject.deliverables.release_1&#xA;REPRESENTATIVE HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH LOSS,&#xA;DAMAGES, CLAIMS OR COSTS. IN ANY EVENT, cleonproject.deliverables.release_1’S AGGREGATE&#xA;LIABILITY AND THAT OF ITS AFFILIATES, SUPPLIERS, AND CERTIFICATE&#xA;AUTHORITIES UNDER OR IN CONNECTION WITH THIS AGREEMENT WILL BE&#xA;LIMITED TO THE AMOUNT PAID FOR THE SOFTWARE, IF ANY. THIS LIMITATION&#xA;WILL APPLY EVEN IN THE EVENT OF A FUNDAMENTAL OR MATERIAL BREACH&#xA;OR A BREACH OF THE FUNDAMENTAL OR MATERIAL TERMS OF THIS AGREEMENT.&#xA;Nothing contained in this agreement limits cleonproject.deliverables.release_1’s liability&#xA;to you in the event of death or personal injury resulting from&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.release_1’s negligence or for the tort of deceit (fraud). cleonproject.deliverables.release_1&#xA;is acting on behalf of its affiliates, suppliers, and Certificate&#xA;Authorities for the purpose of disclaiming, excluding and limiting&#xA;obligations, warranties and liability, but in no other respects&#xA;and for no other purpose. For further information, contact cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.&#xA;THE FOREGOING LIMITATIONS AND EXCLUSIONS APPLY TO THE EXTENT&#xA;PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW IN YOUR JURISDICTION. THIS LIMITATION&#xA;OF LIABILITY MAY NOT BE VALID IN SOME COUNTRIES. YOU MAY HAVE&#xA;RIGHTS THAT CANNOT BE WAIVED UNDER CONSUMER PROTECTION AND OTHER&#xA;LAWS. cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 DOES NOT SEEK TO LIMIT YOUR WARRANTY OR REMEDIES&#xA;TO ANY EXTENT NOT PERMITTED BY LAW. SEE SECTION 14 FOR JURISDICTION-SPECIFIC&#xA;STATEMENTS.&#xA;9. Export Rules.&#xA;You agree that the Software will not be shipped, transferred&#xA;or exported into any country or used in any manner prohibited&#xA;by the United States Export Administration Act or any other export&#xA;laws, restrictions or regulations (collectively the “Export Laws”).&#xA;In addition, if the Software is identified as an export controlled&#xA;item under the Export Laws, you represent and warrant that you&#xA;are not a citizen of, or located within, an embargoed or otherwise&#xA;restricted nation  and that you are not otherwise prohibited&#xA;under the Export Laws from receiving the Software. All rights&#xA;to use the Software are granted on condition that such rights&#xA;are forfeited if you fail to comply with the terms of this agreement.&#xA;10. Governing Law.&#xA;If you are a consumer who uses the Software for only personal&#xA;non-business purposes, then this agreement will be governed by&#xA;the laws of the state in which you purchased the license to use&#xA;the Software. If you are not such a consumer, this agreement&#xA;will be governed by and construed in accordance with the substantive&#xA;laws in force in SWITZERLAND. The commercial court of the canton&#xA;of Aargau shall have non-exclusive jurisdiction over all disputes&#xA;relating to this agreement. This agreement will not be governed&#xA;by the conflict of law rules of any jurisdiction or the United&#xA;Nations Convention on Contracts for the International Sale of&#xA;Goods, the application of which is expressly excluded.&#xA;11. General Provisions.&#xA;If any part of this agreement is found void and unenforceable,&#xA;it will not affect the validity of the balance of this agreement,&#xA;which will remain valid and enforceable according to its terms&#xA;This agreement may only be modified in writing, signed by an&#xA;authorized officer of cleonproject.deliverables.release_1. This is the entire agreement&#xA;between cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 and you relating to the Software and it supersedes&#xA;any prior representations, discussions, undertakings, communications&#xA;or advertising relating to the Software.&#xA;12. Compliance with Licenses.&#xA;If you are a business, company, or organization, you agree that,&#xA;no more than once every 12 months, cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 or its authorized&#xA;representative shall, upon 10 days’ prior notice to you, have&#xA;the right to inspect your records, systems, and facilities to&#xA;verify that your use of any and all cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 software is in&#xA;conformity with your valid licenses from cleonproject.deliverables.release_1. If a verification&#xA;discloses that your use is not in conformity with a valid license,&#xA;you shall immediately obtain valid licenses to bring your use&#xA;into conformity.&#xA;13. Internet Connectivity and Privacy.&#xA;13.1 Automatic Connections to the Internet.&#xA;The Software may cause your Computer to automatically connect&#xA;to the Internet and to communicate with an cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 website&#xA;for purposes that may include providing you with additional information,&#xA;features and functionality. The following provisions apply to&#xA;all automatic Internet connections by the Software:&#xA;13.1.1 When the Software automatically connects to the Internet,&#xA;an Internet protocol address (“IP Address”) that is associated&#xA;with your current Internet connection is sent to an cleonproject.deliverables.release_1&#xA;website;&#xA;13.1.2 When the Software automatically connects to the Internet,&#xA;no personally identifiable information is sent except to the&#xA;extent that IP Addresses may be considered personally identifiable&#xA;in some jurisdictions; and&#xA;13.1.3 Whenever the Software makes an Internet connection and&#xA;communicates with an cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 website, unless you are provided&#xA;with separate terms of use at that time, the cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.com&#xA;Terms of Use (http://www.cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.com) shall apply. Please&#xA;note that the cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 Privacy Policy allows tracking of website&#xA;visits and it addresses in detail the topic of tracking and use&#xA;of cookies, web beacons and similar devices.&#xA;13.1.4 The Software may transmit your serial number and your&#xA;e-mail address you used to register your license to cleonproject.deliverables.release_1&#xA;and in doing so may prevent uses of the Software that are not&#xA;permitted.&#xA;13.2 Updating. The Software may cause your Computer to automatically&#xA;connect to the Internet to check for Updates that are available&#xA;for automatic download to your Computer and to let cleonproject.deliverables.release_1&#xA;know the Software is successfully installed. Please consult the&#xA;Documentation for information about changing default update settings.&#xA;13.4 Use of cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 Online Services. The Software may use&#xA;your Computer to automatically connect to the Internet to facilitate&#xA;your access to content and services that are provided to you&#xA;by cleonproject.deliverables.release_1. Your Software may automatically update downloadable&#xA;materials from these services so as to provide immediate availability&#xA;of these services even when you are offline. Please consult the&#xA;Documentation for information about changing default update settings.&#xA;13.5 Digital Certificates. The Software uses digital certificates&#xA;to help you identify downloaded files (e.g., applications and&#xA;content) and the publishers of those files. Your Computer may&#xA;connect to the Internet at the time of validation of a digital&#xA;certificate.&#xA;14. Specific Provisions and Exceptions.&#xA;This section sets forth specific provisions related to certain&#xA;products and components of the Software as well as limited exceptions&#xA;to the above terms and conditions. To the extent that any provision&#xA;in this section is in conflict with any other term or condition&#xA;in this agreement, this section will supersede such other term&#xA;or condition.&#xA;14.1 No Prejudice, European Union Provisions.&#xA;14.1.1 This agreement will not prejudice the statutory rights&#xA;of any party, including those dealing as consumers. For example,&#xA;for consumers in New Zealand who obtain the Software for personal,&#xA;domestic or household use (not business purposes), this agreement&#xA;is subject to the Consumer Guarantees Act.&#xA;14.1.2 If you obtained the Software in the European Union (EU),&#xA;you usually reside in the EU and you are a consumer (that is&#xA;you use the Software for personal, non-business related purposes),&#xA;then Section 6 does not apply to your purchase and use of the&#xA;Software. Instead, cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 warrants for a period of 2 years&#xA;from purchase that the Software provides the functionalities&#xA;set forth in the Documentation (the “agreed upon functionalities”)&#xA;when used on the recommended hardware configuration. Non-substantial&#xA;variation from the agreed upon functionalities will not establish&#xA;any warranty rights. THIS WARRANTY DOES NOT APPLY TO SOFTWARE&#xA;THAT YOU REQUEST TO USE ON A PRE-RELEASE, TRYOUT, STARTER, PRODUCT&#xA;SAMPLER BASIS, OR TO FONT SOFTWARE CONVERTED INTO OTHER FORMATS&#xA;OR TO THE EXTENT THE SOFTWARE FAILS TO PERFORM BECAUSE IT HAS&#xA;BEEN ALTERED BY YOU. To make a warranty claim, you must notify&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 during this 2 year period, providing details of proof&#xA;of purchase of the Software. cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 will verify with you&#xA;whether there is a defect in the Software or advise you that&#xA;the error arises because you have not installed the Software&#xA;correctly (in which case, cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 shall assist you). If there&#xA;is a defect in the Software, you may request from cleonproject.deliverables.release_1&#xA;either a refund or a repaired/replacement copy of the Software.&#xA;Requests must be accompanied by proof of purchase. In the event&#xA;your warranty details are substantiated, cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 will meet&#xA;your request for repaired/replacement Software, unless it is&#xA;not reasonable for cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 to do so, in which case cleonproject.deliverables.release_1&#xA;will provide you with a refund. For warranty assistance, please&#xA;contact cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.&#xA;Please note that the provisions of Section 8 (Limitation of Liability)&#xA;will continue to apply to any damages claims you make in respect&#xA;of your use of the Software. Nonetheless, cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 shall be&#xA;liable for direct losses that are reasonably foreseeable in the&#xA;event of a breach by cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 of this agreement. You are advised&#xA;to take all reasonable measures to avoid and reduce damages,&#xA;in particular by making back-up copies of the Software and your&#xA;computer data.&#xA;This agreement, and in particular, this Section 14.1.2, is intended&#xA;to describe your rights (including your statutory rights) in&#xA;the event there should be problems with your use of the Software.&#xA;If your statutory rights should be greater than this description,&#xA;your statutory rights shall apply.&#xA;14.2 Pre-release Software Additional Terms. If the Software is&#xA;pre-commercial release or beta software (“Pre-release Software”),&#xA;then this section applies. The Pre-release Software is a pre-release&#xA;version, does not represent final product from cleonproject.deliverables.release_1, and&#xA;may contain bugs, errors and other problems that could cause&#xA;system or other failures and data loss. cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 may never&#xA;commercially release the Pre-release Software. If you received&#xA;the Pre-release Software pursuant to a separate written agreement&#xA;your use of the Software is also governed by such agreement.&#xA;You will return or destroy all copies of Pre-release Software&#xA;upon request by cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 or upon cleonproject.deliverables.release_1’s commercial&#xA;release of such Software. YOUR USE OF PRE-RELEASE SOFTWARE IS&#xA;AT YOUR OWN RISK. SEE SECTIONS 7 AND 8 FOR WARRANTY DISCLAIMERS&#xA;AND LIABILITY LIMITATIONS WHICH GOVERN PRE-RELEASE SOFTWARE.&#xA;If you have any questions regarding this agreement or if you&#xA;wish to request any information from cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 please use the&#xA;address and contact information included with this product to&#xA;contact cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 is a registered trademark of cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 in the Switzerland&#xA;and/or other countries. All other trademarks are the property&#xA;of their respective owners.
        </license>
      </licenses>
      <copyright uri='http://www.zwyssig.info/copyright' url='http://www.zwyssig.info/copyright'>
        Zwyssig Informatik GmbH
      </copyright>
    </unit>
    <unit id='cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.feature.group' version='0.2.2' singleton='false'>
      <update id='cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.feature.group' range='[0.0.0,0.2.2)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='4'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='cleonproject.deliverables.architecture'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='No description available'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description.url' value='http://www.zwyssig.info/description'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.type.group' value='true'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='1'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.feature.group' version='0.2.2'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='27'>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='ch.actifsource.core' range='9.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='ch.actifsource.environment' range='9.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='ch.actifsource.util' range='9.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='ch.actifsource.generator' range='9.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='ch.actifsource.ui.wizard.generic' range='9.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='ch.actifsource.ui.wizard' range='9.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='ch.actifsource.xml' range='9.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.deployment.chocolatey.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.implementation.gradle.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.support.documentation.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.initialization.projectmanagement.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.initialization.processlanguage.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.common.importwizard.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.common.doc.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.common.resources.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.common.xml.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.conception.actifsource.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.conception.applications.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.conception.platform.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.conception.network.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.conception.architecture.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.common.glossary.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.common.analysis.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.implementation.plantuml.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleon.conception.testing.feature.group' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.model.architecture.builtin' range='[0.2.2,0.2.2]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.feature.jar' range='[0.2.2,0.2.2]'>
          <filter>
            (org.eclipse.update.install.features=true)
          </filter>
        </required>
      </requires>
      <touchpoint id='null' version='0.0.0'/>
      <licenses size='1'>
        <license uri='http://www.zwyssig.info/license' url='http://www.zwyssig.info/license'>
          cleonproject.deliverables.architecture Software License Agreement&#xA;NOTICE TO USER: PLEASE READ THIS AGREEMENT CAREFULLY. BY COPYING,&#xA;INSTALLING OR USING ALL OR ANY PORTION OF THE SOFTWARE YOU ACCEPT&#xA;ALL THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS AGREEMENT, INCLUDING, IN&#xA;PARTICULAR THE PROVISIONS ON: TRANSFERABILITY IN SECTION 4; WARRANTY&#xA;IN SECTIONS 6 AND 7; LIABILITY IN SECTION 8; CONNECTIVITY AND&#xA;PRIVACY IN SECTION 13; AND SPECIFIC PROVISIONS AND EXCEPTIONS&#xA;IN SECTION 14. YOU AGREE THAT THIS AGREEMENT IS LIKE ANY WRITTEN&#xA;NEGOTIATED AGREEMENT SIGNED BY YOU. THIS AGREEMENT IS ENFORCEABLE&#xA;AGAINST YOU AND ANY LEGAL ENTITY THAT OBTAINED THE SOFTWARE AND&#xA;ON WHOSE BEHALF IT IS USED: FOR EXAMPLE, IF APPLICABLE, YOUR&#xA;EMPLOYER. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS AGREEMENT,&#xA;DO NOT USE AND/OR BUY THE SOFTWARE.&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.architecture AND ITS SUPPLIERS OWN ALL INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY IN&#xA;THE SOFTWARE. THE SOFTWARE IS LICENSED, NOT SOLD. cleonproject.deliverables.architecture&#xA;PERMITS YOU TO COPY, DOWNLOAD, INSTALL, USE, OR OTHERWISE BENEFIT&#xA;FROM THE FUNCTIONALITY OR INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY OF THE SOFTWARE&#xA;ONLY IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS AGREEMENT. USE OF SOME&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.architecture AND SOME THIRD PARTY MATERIALS AND SERVICES INCLUDED&#xA;IN OR ACCESSED THROUGH THE SOFTWARE MAY BE SUBJECT TO OTHER TERMS&#xA;AND CONDITIONS TYPICALLY FOUND IN A SEPARATE LICENSE AGREEMENT,&#xA;TERMS OF USE OR “READ ME” FILE LOCATED WITHIN OR NEAR SUCH MATERIALS&#xA;AND SERVICES OR AT http://www.zwyssig.info.&#xA;THE SOFTWARE MAY CAUSE YOUR COMPUTER TO AUTOMATICALLY CONNECT&#xA;TO THE INTERNET. SEE SECTIONS 13 AND 14 FOR ADDITIONAL INFORMATION.&#xA;THE SOFTWARE MAY INCLUDE PRODUCT ACTIVATION AND OTHER TECHNOLOGY&#xA;DESIGNED TO PREVENT UNAUTHORIZED USE AND COPYING. THIS TECHNOLOGY&#xA;MAY CAUSE YOUR COMPUTER TO AUTOMATICALLY CONNECT TO THE INTERNET&#xA;AS DESCRIBED IN SECTION 13. ADDITIONALLY, ONCE CONNECTED, THE&#xA;SOFTWARE MAY TRANSMIT YOUR SERIAL NUMBER TO cleonproject.deliverables.architecture AND IN&#xA;DOING SO MAY PREVENT USES OF THE SOFTWARE THAT ARE NOT PERMITTED.&#xA;VISIT http://www.cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.com FOR ADDITIONAL INFORMATION ABOUT&#xA;PRODUCT ACTIVATION.&#xA;1. Definitions.&#xA;“cleonproject.deliverables.architecture” means Zwyssig Informatik GmbH, &#xA;Switzerland.&#xA;“Computer” means a virtual or physical computer device that accepts&#xA;information in digital or similar form and manipulates it for&#xA;a specific result based on a sequence of instructions.&#xA;“Internal Network” means a private, proprietary network resource&#xA;accessible only by employees and individual contractors (i.e.,&#xA;temporary employees) of a specific corporation or similar business&#xA;entity. Internal Network does not include portions of the Internet&#xA;or any other network community open to the public, such as membership&#xA;or subscription driven groups, associations and similar organizations.&#xA;“Output File” means an output file you create with the Software.&#xA;“Permitted Number” means one (1) unless otherwise indicated under&#xA;a valid license (e.g., volume license) granted by cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.&#xA;“Software” means (a) all of the information with which this agreement&#xA;is provided, including but not limited to (i) cleonproject.deliverables.architecture or&#xA;third party software files and other computer information; (ii)&#xA;sample files bundled with cleonproject.deliverables.architecture software or obtained from&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.architecture through a separate service; (iii) related explanatory&#xA;written materials and files (“Documentation”); and (b) any modified&#xA;versions and copies of, and upgrades, updates and additions to,&#xA;such information, provided to you by cleonproject.deliverables.architecture at any time,&#xA;to the extent not provided under a separate agreement (collectively,&#xA;“Updates”).&#xA;2. Software License.&#xA;If you obtained the Software and any required serial number(s)&#xA;from cleonproject.deliverables.architecture or one of its authorized licensees and as long&#xA;as you comply with the terms of this agreement, cleonproject.deliverables.architecture grants&#xA;you a non-exclusive license to install and use the Software in&#xA;a manner consistent with its design and Documentation and as&#xA;further set forth below. See Section 14 for specific provisions&#xA;related to the use of certain products and components.&#xA;2.1 General Use. You may install and use one copy of the Software&#xA;on up to the Permitted Number of your compatible Computers as&#xA;long as, when required by the Software, you present a valid serial&#xA;number for each copy; and&#xA;2.2 Distribution from Server. You may copy an image of the Software&#xA;onto file server(s) within your Internal Network for the purpose&#xA;of downloading and installing the Software onto Computers within&#xA;the same Internal Network for use as permitted by Section 2.1;&#xA;and&#xA;2.3 Server Use. You may install the Software on Computer file&#xA;server(s) within your Internal Network only for use of the Software&#xA;initiated by an individual from a Computer within the same Internal&#xA;Network as permitted by Section 2.1. The total number of users&#xA;(not the concurrent number of users) able to use the Software&#xA;on such Computer file server(s) may not exceed the Permitted&#xA;Number. By way of example, the foregoing does not permit you&#xA;to install or access (either directly or through commands, data&#xA;or instructions) the Software: (i) from or to a Computer not&#xA;part of your Internal Network, (ii) for enabling web hosted workgroups&#xA;or services available to the public, (iii) by any individual&#xA;or entity to use, download, copy or otherwise benefit from the&#xA;functionality of the Software unless licensed to do so by cleonproject.deliverables.architecture,&#xA;(iv) as a component of a system, workflow or service accessible&#xA;by more than the Permitted Number of users, or (v) for operations&#xA;not initiated by an individual user (e.g., automated server processing);&#xA;and&#xA;2.4 Backup Copy. You may make a reasonable number of backup copies&#xA;of the Software, provided your backup copies are not installed&#xA;or used for other than archival purposes.&#xA;2.5 Sample Application Code. You may modify the source code form&#xA;of those portions of such software programs that are identified&#xA;as sample code, sample application code, or components (each,&#xA;“Sample Application Code”) in the accompanying Documentation&#xA;solely for the purposes of designing, developing and testing&#xA;applications developed using cleonproject.deliverables.architecture software programs; provided,&#xA;however, you are permitted to copy and distribute the Sample&#xA;Application Code (modified or unmodified) only if all of the&#xA;following conditions are met: (1) you distribute the compiled&#xA;object Sample Application Code with your application; (2) you&#xA;do not include the Sample Application Code in any product or&#xA;application designed for software development; and (3) you do&#xA;not use the cleonproject.deliverables.architecture name, logos or other cleonproject.deliverables.architecture trademarks&#xA;to market your application. You agree to indemnify, hold harmless&#xA;and defend cleonproject.deliverables.architecture from and against any loss, damage, claims&#xA;or lawsuits, including attorney’s fees, that arise or result&#xA;from the use or distribution of your application. You may be&#xA;granted additional rights to modify or distribute cleonproject.deliverables.architecture&#xA;software code within documentation relating to such code and/or&#xA;the Software or in a separate agreement between you and cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.&#xA;2.6 Tryout Software. The Software, or portions of the Software,&#xA;may be configured to allow trial or tryout for a limited period&#xA;of time or for a limited number of launches. You are not permitted&#xA;to use the Software in a manner inconsistent with its design&#xA;or Documentation. For example, you may not use the Software after&#xA;its tryout period has ended unless you input a valid serial number.&#xA;ACCESS TO ANY OUTPUT FILES CREATED WITH THE SOFTWARE USED ON&#xA;A TRYOUT OR TRIAL BASIS IS ENTIRELY AT YOUR OWN RISK.&#xA;3. Intellectual Property Ownership.&#xA;The Software and any authorized copies that you make are the&#xA;intellectual property of and are owned by cleonproject.deliverables.architecture and its&#xA;suppliers. The structure, organization and code of the Software&#xA;are the valuable trade secrets and confidential information of&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.architecture and its suppliers. The Software is protected by law,&#xA;including but not limited to the copyright laws of the Switzerland&#xA;and other countries, and by international treaty provisions.&#xA;Except as expressly stated herein, this agreement does not grant&#xA;you any intellectual property rights in the Software and all&#xA;rights not expressly granted are reserved by cleonproject.deliverables.architecture and&#xA;its suppliers.&#xA;4. Restrictions and Requirements.&#xA;4.1 Notices. Any permitted copy of the Software that you make&#xA;must contain the same copyright and other proprietary notices&#xA;that appear on or in the Software.&#xA;4.2 Use Obligations. You agree that you will not use the Software&#xA;other than as permitted by this agreement and that you will not&#xA;use the Software in a manner inconsistent with its design or&#xA;Documentation.&#xA;4.3 No Modifications. Except as permitted in Section 14, you&#xA;may not modify, adapt or translate the Software.&#xA;4.4 No Reverse Engineering. You will not reverse engineer, decompile,&#xA;disassemble or otherwise attempt to discover the source code&#xA;of the Software except to the extent you may be expressly permitted&#xA;under applicable law to decompile only in order to achieve interoperability&#xA;with the Software.&#xA;4.5 No Unbundling. The Software may include various applications,&#xA;utilities and components, may support multiple platforms and&#xA;languages and may be provided to you on multiple media or in&#xA;multiple copies. Nonetheless, the Software is designed and provided&#xA;to you as a single product to be used as a single product on&#xA;Computers as permitted by Sections 2 and 14. You are not required&#xA;to install all component parts of the Software, but you may not&#xA;unbundle the component parts of the Software for use on different&#xA;Computers. You may not unbundle or repackage the Software for&#xA;distribution, transfer or resale. See Section 14 for specific&#xA;exceptions to this Section 4.5.&#xA;4.6 No Transfer. YOU WILL NOT RENT, LEASE, SELL, SUBLICENSE,&#xA;ASSIGN OR TRANSFER YOUR RIGHTS IN THE SOFTWARE, OR AUTHORIZE&#xA;ANY PORTION OF THE SOFTWARE TO BE COPIED ONTO ANOTHER INDIVIDUAL&#xA;OR LEGAL ENTITY’S COMPUTER EXCEPT AS MAY BE EXPRESSLY PERMITTED&#xA;HEREIN. You may, however, permanently transfer all your rights&#xA;to use the Software to another individual or legal entity provided&#xA;that: (a) you also transfer (i) this agreement, (ii) the serial&#xA;number(s), the Software affixed to media provided by cleonproject.deliverables.architecture&#xA;or its authorized distributor, and all other software or hardware&#xA;bundled, packaged or pre-installed with the Software, including&#xA;all copies, upgrades, updates and prior versions, to such individual&#xA;or entity; (b) you retain no upgrades, updates or copies, including&#xA;backups and copies stored on a Computer; and (c) the receiving&#xA;party accepts the terms and conditions of this agreement and&#xA;any other terms and conditions under which you purchased a valid&#xA;license to the Software. NOTWITHSTANDING THE FOREGOING, YOU MAY&#xA;NOT TRANSFER EDUCATION, PRERELEASE,&#xA;OR NOT FOR RESALE COPIES OF THE SOFTWARE. Prior to a transfer&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.architecture may require that you and the receiving party confirm&#xA;in writing your compliance with this agreement, provide cleonproject.deliverables.architecture&#xA;with information about yourselves, and register as end-users&#xA;of the Software. Allow 4-6 weeks to&#xA;transfer. Please visit http://www.cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.com or contact&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.architecture for more information.&#xA;4.7 No Service Bureau. You will not use or offer the Software&#xA;on a service bureau basis. By way of example, you are not allowed&#xA;to offer the Software as a service (SaaS).&#xA;5. Updates.&#xA;If the Software is an upgrade or update to a previous version&#xA;of cleonproject.deliverables.architecture software, you must possess a valid license to&#xA;such previous version in order to use such upgrade or update.&#xA;After you install such update or upgrade, you may continue to&#xA;use any such previous version in accordance with its end-user&#xA;license agreement only if (a) the upgrade or update and all previous&#xA;versions are installed on the same Computer, (b) the previous&#xA;versions or copies thereof are not transferred to another party&#xA;or device unless all copies of the update or upgrade are also&#xA;transferred to such party or device and (c) you acknowledge that&#xA;any obligation cleonproject.deliverables.architecture may have to support the previous version(s)&#xA;may end upon the availability of the upgrade or update. No other&#xA;use of the previous version(s) is permitted after installation&#xA;of an update or upgrade. Upgrades and updates may be licensed&#xA;to you by cleonproject.deliverables.architecture with additional or different terms.&#xA;6. LIMITED WARRANTY.&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.architecture warrants to the individual or entity that first purchases&#xA;a license for the Software for use pursuant to the terms of this&#xA;agreement that the Software will perform substantially in accordance&#xA;with the Documentation for the ninety (90) day period following&#xA;receipt of the Software when used on the recommended operating&#xA;system and hardware configuration. Non-substantial variation&#xA;of performance from the Documentation does not establish a warranty&#xA;right. This limited warranty does not apply to the following,&#xA;which are made available AS-IS and without warranty from cleonproject.deliverables.architecture:&#xA;patches, pre-release (beta), trial, starter, evaluation, product&#xA;sampler, and not for resale (NFR) copies of the Software; websites,&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.architecture Online Services; Third Party Online Services; and&#xA;any software made available by cleonproject.deliverables.architecture for free via web download&#xA;from an cleonproject.deliverables.architecture website. All warranty claims must be made,&#xA;along with proof of purchase, to cleonproject.deliverables.architecture within such ninety&#xA;(90) day period. Visit the cleonproject.deliverables.architecture website at http://www.cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.com&#xA;for more information about warranty claims. If the Software does&#xA;not perform substantially in accordance with the Documentation,&#xA;the entire liability of cleonproject.deliverables.architecture and its affiliates and your&#xA;exclusive remedy will be limited to either, at cleonproject.deliverables.architecture’s&#xA;option, replacement of the Software or refund of the license&#xA;fee you paid for the Software. THE LIMITED WARRANTY SET FORTH&#xA;IN THIS SECTION GIVES YOU SPECIFIC LEGAL RIGHTS. YOU MAY HAVE&#xA;ADDITIONAL RIGHTS UNDER LAW WHICH VARY FROM JURISDICTION TO JURISDICTION.&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.architecture DOES NOT SEEK TO LIMIT YOUR WARRANTY RIGHTS TO ANY&#xA;EXTENT NOT PERMITTED BY LAW. Please see Section 14 for jurisdiction-specific&#xA;provisions or contact cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.&#xA;7. DISCLAIMER.&#xA;THE FOREGOING LIMITED WARRANTY IS THE ONLY WARRANTY OFFERED BY&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.architecture AND ITS AFFILIATES AND IT STATES THE SOLE AND EXCLUSIVE&#xA;REMEDIES FOR cleonproject.deliverables.architecture’S, ITS AFFILIATES’ OR SUPPLIERS’ BREACH&#xA;OF THAT OFFERED WARRANTY. THE FOREGOING OFFERED WARRANTY AND&#xA;ANY STATUTORY WARRANTY AND REMEDY THAT CANNOT BE EXCLUDED OR&#xA;LIMITED UNDER LAW ARE THE ONLY WARRANTIES APPLICABLE TO THE SOFTWARE.&#xA;OTHER THAN THOSE OFFERED AND STATUTORY WARRANTIES AND REMEDIES,&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.architecture, ITS AFFILIATES, SUPPLIERS AND CERTIFICATE AUTHORITIES&#xA;(DEFINED BELOW) DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES, CONDITIONS, REPRESENTATIONS&#xA;AND TERMS, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, WHETHER BY STATUTE, COMMON LAW,&#xA;CUSTOM, USAGE OR OTHERWISE AS TO ANY MATTER, INCLUDING BUT NOT&#xA;LIMITED TO PERFORMANCE, SECURITY, NON-INFRINGEMENT OF THIRD PARTY&#xA;RIGHTS, INTEGRATION, MERCHANTABILITY, QUIET ENJOYMENT, SATISFACTORY&#xA;QUALITY AND FITNESS FOR ANY PARTICULAR PURPOSE. OTHER THAN SUCH&#xA;OFFERED AND STATUTORY WARRANTIES AND REMEDIES, cleonproject.deliverables.architecture AND&#xA;ITS SUPPLIERS PROVIDE THE SOFTWARE AND ACCESS TO ANY WEBSITES,&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.architecture OR THIRD PARTY ONLINE SERVICES AND CERTIFICATE AUTHORITY&#xA;SERVICES AS-IS AND WITH ALL FAULTS. THIS DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTY&#xA;MAY NOT BE VALID IN SOME STATES. YOU MAY HAVE ADDITIONAL WARRANTY&#xA;RIGHTS UNDER LAW WHICH MAY NOT BE WAIVED OR DISCLAIMED. cleonproject.deliverables.architecture&#xA;DOES NOT SEEK TO LIMIT YOUR WARRANTY RIGHTS TO ANY EXTENT NOT&#xA;PERMITTED BY LAW. The provisions of Sections 7 and Section 8&#xA;will survive the termination of this agreement, howsoever caused,&#xA;but this will not imply or create any continued right to use&#xA;the Software after termination of this agreement.&#xA;8. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY.&#xA;EXCEPT FOR THE EXCLUSIVE REMEDY OFFERED BY cleonproject.deliverables.architecture ABOVE&#xA;AND ANY REMEDIES THAT CANNOT BE EXCLUDED OR LIMITED UNDER LAW,&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.architecture, ITS AFFILIATES, SUPPLIERS, OR CERTIFICATE AUTHORITIES&#xA;WILL NOT BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR ANY LOSS, DAMAGES, CLAIMS OR COSTS&#xA;WHATSOEVER INCLUDING ANY CONSEQUENTIAL, INDIRECT OR INCIDENTAL&#xA;DAMAGES, ANY LOST PROFITS OR LOST SAVINGS, ANY DAMAGES RESULTING&#xA;FROM BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, PERSONAL INJURY OR FAILURE TO MEET&#xA;ANY DUTY OF CARE, OR CLAIMS BY A THIRD PARTY, EVEN IF AN cleonproject.deliverables.architecture&#xA;REPRESENTATIVE HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH LOSS,&#xA;DAMAGES, CLAIMS OR COSTS. IN ANY EVENT, cleonproject.deliverables.architecture’S AGGREGATE&#xA;LIABILITY AND THAT OF ITS AFFILIATES, SUPPLIERS, AND CERTIFICATE&#xA;AUTHORITIES UNDER OR IN CONNECTION WITH THIS AGREEMENT WILL BE&#xA;LIMITED TO THE AMOUNT PAID FOR THE SOFTWARE, IF ANY. THIS LIMITATION&#xA;WILL APPLY EVEN IN THE EVENT OF A FUNDAMENTAL OR MATERIAL BREACH&#xA;OR A BREACH OF THE FUNDAMENTAL OR MATERIAL TERMS OF THIS AGREEMENT.&#xA;Nothing contained in this agreement limits cleonproject.deliverables.architecture’s liability&#xA;to you in the event of death or personal injury resulting from&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.architecture’s negligence or for the tort of deceit (fraud). cleonproject.deliverables.architecture&#xA;is acting on behalf of its affiliates, suppliers, and Certificate&#xA;Authorities for the purpose of disclaiming, excluding and limiting&#xA;obligations, warranties and liability, but in no other respects&#xA;and for no other purpose. For further information, contact cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.&#xA;THE FOREGOING LIMITATIONS AND EXCLUSIONS APPLY TO THE EXTENT&#xA;PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW IN YOUR JURISDICTION. THIS LIMITATION&#xA;OF LIABILITY MAY NOT BE VALID IN SOME COUNTRIES. YOU MAY HAVE&#xA;RIGHTS THAT CANNOT BE WAIVED UNDER CONSUMER PROTECTION AND OTHER&#xA;LAWS. cleonproject.deliverables.architecture DOES NOT SEEK TO LIMIT YOUR WARRANTY OR REMEDIES&#xA;TO ANY EXTENT NOT PERMITTED BY LAW. SEE SECTION 14 FOR JURISDICTION-SPECIFIC&#xA;STATEMENTS.&#xA;9. Export Rules.&#xA;You agree that the Software will not be shipped, transferred&#xA;or exported into any country or used in any manner prohibited&#xA;by the United States Export Administration Act or any other export&#xA;laws, restrictions or regulations (collectively the “Export Laws”).&#xA;In addition, if the Software is identified as an export controlled&#xA;item under the Export Laws, you represent and warrant that you&#xA;are not a citizen of, or located within, an embargoed or otherwise&#xA;restricted nation  and that you are not otherwise prohibited&#xA;under the Export Laws from receiving the Software. All rights&#xA;to use the Software are granted on condition that such rights&#xA;are forfeited if you fail to comply with the terms of this agreement.&#xA;10. Governing Law.&#xA;If you are a consumer who uses the Software for only personal&#xA;non-business purposes, then this agreement will be governed by&#xA;the laws of the state in which you purchased the license to use&#xA;the Software. If you are not such a consumer, this agreement&#xA;will be governed by and construed in accordance with the substantive&#xA;laws in force in SWITZERLAND. The commercial court of the canton&#xA;of Aargau shall have non-exclusive jurisdiction over all disputes&#xA;relating to this agreement. This agreement will not be governed&#xA;by the conflict of law rules of any jurisdiction or the United&#xA;Nations Convention on Contracts for the International Sale of&#xA;Goods, the application of which is expressly excluded.&#xA;11. General Provisions.&#xA;If any part of this agreement is found void and unenforceable,&#xA;it will not affect the validity of the balance of this agreement,&#xA;which will remain valid and enforceable according to its terms&#xA;This agreement may only be modified in writing, signed by an&#xA;authorized officer of cleonproject.deliverables.architecture. This is the entire agreement&#xA;between cleonproject.deliverables.architecture and you relating to the Software and it supersedes&#xA;any prior representations, discussions, undertakings, communications&#xA;or advertising relating to the Software.&#xA;12. Compliance with Licenses.&#xA;If you are a business, company, or organization, you agree that,&#xA;no more than once every 12 months, cleonproject.deliverables.architecture or its authorized&#xA;representative shall, upon 10 days’ prior notice to you, have&#xA;the right to inspect your records, systems, and facilities to&#xA;verify that your use of any and all cleonproject.deliverables.architecture software is in&#xA;conformity with your valid licenses from cleonproject.deliverables.architecture. If a verification&#xA;discloses that your use is not in conformity with a valid license,&#xA;you shall immediately obtain valid licenses to bring your use&#xA;into conformity.&#xA;13. Internet Connectivity and Privacy.&#xA;13.1 Automatic Connections to the Internet.&#xA;The Software may cause your Computer to automatically connect&#xA;to the Internet and to communicate with an cleonproject.deliverables.architecture website&#xA;for purposes that may include providing you with additional information,&#xA;features and functionality. The following provisions apply to&#xA;all automatic Internet connections by the Software:&#xA;13.1.1 When the Software automatically connects to the Internet,&#xA;an Internet protocol address (“IP Address”) that is associated&#xA;with your current Internet connection is sent to an cleonproject.deliverables.architecture&#xA;website;&#xA;13.1.2 When the Software automatically connects to the Internet,&#xA;no personally identifiable information is sent except to the&#xA;extent that IP Addresses may be considered personally identifiable&#xA;in some jurisdictions; and&#xA;13.1.3 Whenever the Software makes an Internet connection and&#xA;communicates with an cleonproject.deliverables.architecture website, unless you are provided&#xA;with separate terms of use at that time, the cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.com&#xA;Terms of Use (http://www.cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.com) shall apply. Please&#xA;note that the cleonproject.deliverables.architecture Privacy Policy allows tracking of website&#xA;visits and it addresses in detail the topic of tracking and use&#xA;of cookies, web beacons and similar devices.&#xA;13.1.4 The Software may transmit your serial number and your&#xA;e-mail address you used to register your license to cleonproject.deliverables.architecture&#xA;and in doing so may prevent uses of the Software that are not&#xA;permitted.&#xA;13.2 Updating. The Software may cause your Computer to automatically&#xA;connect to the Internet to check for Updates that are available&#xA;for automatic download to your Computer and to let cleonproject.deliverables.architecture&#xA;know the Software is successfully installed. Please consult the&#xA;Documentation for information about changing default update settings.&#xA;13.4 Use of cleonproject.deliverables.architecture Online Services. The Software may use&#xA;your Computer to automatically connect to the Internet to facilitate&#xA;your access to content and services that are provided to you&#xA;by cleonproject.deliverables.architecture. Your Software may automatically update downloadable&#xA;materials from these services so as to provide immediate availability&#xA;of these services even when you are offline. Please consult the&#xA;Documentation for information about changing default update settings.&#xA;13.5 Digital Certificates. The Software uses digital certificates&#xA;to help you identify downloaded files (e.g., applications and&#xA;content) and the publishers of those files. Your Computer may&#xA;connect to the Internet at the time of validation of a digital&#xA;certificate.&#xA;14. Specific Provisions and Exceptions.&#xA;This section sets forth specific provisions related to certain&#xA;products and components of the Software as well as limited exceptions&#xA;to the above terms and conditions. To the extent that any provision&#xA;in this section is in conflict with any other term or condition&#xA;in this agreement, this section will supersede such other term&#xA;or condition.&#xA;14.1 No Prejudice, European Union Provisions.&#xA;14.1.1 This agreement will not prejudice the statutory rights&#xA;of any party, including those dealing as consumers. For example,&#xA;for consumers in New Zealand who obtain the Software for personal,&#xA;domestic or household use (not business purposes), this agreement&#xA;is subject to the Consumer Guarantees Act.&#xA;14.1.2 If you obtained the Software in the European Union (EU),&#xA;you usually reside in the EU and you are a consumer (that is&#xA;you use the Software for personal, non-business related purposes),&#xA;then Section 6 does not apply to your purchase and use of the&#xA;Software. Instead, cleonproject.deliverables.architecture warrants for a period of 2 years&#xA;from purchase that the Software provides the functionalities&#xA;set forth in the Documentation (the “agreed upon functionalities”)&#xA;when used on the recommended hardware configuration. Non-substantial&#xA;variation from the agreed upon functionalities will not establish&#xA;any warranty rights. THIS WARRANTY DOES NOT APPLY TO SOFTWARE&#xA;THAT YOU REQUEST TO USE ON A PRE-RELEASE, TRYOUT, STARTER, PRODUCT&#xA;SAMPLER BASIS, OR TO FONT SOFTWARE CONVERTED INTO OTHER FORMATS&#xA;OR TO THE EXTENT THE SOFTWARE FAILS TO PERFORM BECAUSE IT HAS&#xA;BEEN ALTERED BY YOU. To make a warranty claim, you must notify&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.architecture during this 2 year period, providing details of proof&#xA;of purchase of the Software. cleonproject.deliverables.architecture will verify with you&#xA;whether there is a defect in the Software or advise you that&#xA;the error arises because you have not installed the Software&#xA;correctly (in which case, cleonproject.deliverables.architecture shall assist you). If there&#xA;is a defect in the Software, you may request from cleonproject.deliverables.architecture&#xA;either a refund or a repaired/replacement copy of the Software.&#xA;Requests must be accompanied by proof of purchase. In the event&#xA;your warranty details are substantiated, cleonproject.deliverables.architecture will meet&#xA;your request for repaired/replacement Software, unless it is&#xA;not reasonable for cleonproject.deliverables.architecture to do so, in which case cleonproject.deliverables.architecture&#xA;will provide you with a refund. For warranty assistance, please&#xA;contact cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.&#xA;Please note that the provisions of Section 8 (Limitation of Liability)&#xA;will continue to apply to any damages claims you make in respect&#xA;of your use of the Software. Nonetheless, cleonproject.deliverables.architecture shall be&#xA;liable for direct losses that are reasonably foreseeable in the&#xA;event of a breach by cleonproject.deliverables.architecture of this agreement. You are advised&#xA;to take all reasonable measures to avoid and reduce damages,&#xA;in particular by making back-up copies of the Software and your&#xA;computer data.&#xA;This agreement, and in particular, this Section 14.1.2, is intended&#xA;to describe your rights (including your statutory rights) in&#xA;the event there should be problems with your use of the Software.&#xA;If your statutory rights should be greater than this description,&#xA;your statutory rights shall apply.&#xA;14.2 Pre-release Software Additional Terms. If the Software is&#xA;pre-commercial release or beta software (“Pre-release Software”),&#xA;then this section applies. The Pre-release Software is a pre-release&#xA;version, does not represent final product from cleonproject.deliverables.architecture, and&#xA;may contain bugs, errors and other problems that could cause&#xA;system or other failures and data loss. cleonproject.deliverables.architecture may never&#xA;commercially release the Pre-release Software. If you received&#xA;the Pre-release Software pursuant to a separate written agreement&#xA;your use of the Software is also governed by such agreement.&#xA;You will return or destroy all copies of Pre-release Software&#xA;upon request by cleonproject.deliverables.architecture or upon cleonproject.deliverables.architecture’s commercial&#xA;release of such Software. YOUR USE OF PRE-RELEASE SOFTWARE IS&#xA;AT YOUR OWN RISK. SEE SECTIONS 7 AND 8 FOR WARRANTY DISCLAIMERS&#xA;AND LIABILITY LIMITATIONS WHICH GOVERN PRE-RELEASE SOFTWARE.&#xA;If you have any questions regarding this agreement or if you&#xA;wish to request any information from cleonproject.deliverables.architecture please use the&#xA;address and contact information included with this product to&#xA;contact cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.architecture is a registered trademark of cleonproject.deliverables.architecture in the Switzerland&#xA;and/or other countries. All other trademarks are the property&#xA;of their respective owners.
        </license>
      </licenses>
      <copyright uri='http://www.zwyssig.info/copyright' url='http://www.zwyssig.info/copyright'>
        Zwyssig Informatik GmbH
      </copyright>
    </unit>
    <unit id='cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.model.architecture.builtin' version='0.2.2'>
      <update id='cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.model.architecture.builtin' range='[0.0.0,0.2.2)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='1'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.model.architecture'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='5'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.model.architecture.builtin' version='0.2.2'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.model.architecture.builtin' version='0.2.2'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.model.architecture' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.model.architecture.javamodel' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='bundle' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='45'>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='ch.actifsource.core' range='9.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='ch.actifsource.environment' range='9.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='ch.actifsource.util' range='9.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='ch.actifsource.xml' range='9.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='ch.actifsource.template' range='9.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='ch.actifsource.ui.wizard.generic' range='9.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='ch.actifsource.ui.wizard' range='9.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.eclipse.core.runtime' range='3.13.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.initialization.projectmanagement.template.versionone.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.conception.architecture.template.xmi.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.initialization.projectmanagement.template.tj3.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.conception.actifsource.model.plugins.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.implementation.gradle.template.gradle.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.support.documentation.template.asciidoc.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.support.documentation.template.docbook.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.initialization.projectmanagement.spec.projectmanagement.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.common.xml.spec.xml.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.initialization.projectmanagement.spec.planning.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.initialization.projectmanagement.spec.resource.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.common.doc.spec.doc.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.common.resources.spec.calendar.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.common.resources.spec.resources.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.initialization.projectmanagement.model.hermes.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.initialization.projectmanagement.spec.hermes.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.common.importwizard.template.java.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.common.importwizard.spec.xml2asrc.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.conception.architecture.spec.eamod.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.conception.architecture.spec.uml.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.common.glossary.spec.glossary.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.common.xml.spec.xmi.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.conception.architecture.spec.buildingblock.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.initialization.projectmanagement.spec.steering.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.conception.actifsource.spec.actifsource.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.conception.applications.spec.arc42.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.conception.platform.spec.arc42.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.conception.architecture.spec.arc42.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.implementation.gradle.spec.plugin.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.conception.actifsource.template.eclipse.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.common.doc.template.asciidoc.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.implementation.plantuml.template.uml.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.conception.testing.spec.testing.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.conception.architecture.spec.analysis.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.common.analysis.spec.analysis.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.common.doc.template.docbook.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='ch.actifsource.generator' range='9.0.0'/>
      </requires>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.model.architecture.builtin' version='0.2.2'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-SymbolicName: cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.model.architecture.builtin;singleton:=true&#xA;Bundle-Version: 0.2.2
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
    <unit id='cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.feature.jar' version='0.2.2'>
      <properties size='3'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='cleonproject.deliverables.release_1'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='No description available'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description.url' value='http://www.zwyssig.info/description'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='3'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.feature.jar' version='0.2.2'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='feature' version='1.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.update.feature' name='cleonproject.deliverables.release_1' version='0.2.2'/>
      </provides>
      <filter>
        (org.eclipse.update.install.features=true)
      </filter>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='org.eclipse.update.feature' id='cleonproject.deliverables.release_1' version='0.2.2'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='zipped'>
            true
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
      <licenses size='1'>
        <license uri='http://www.zwyssig.info/license' url='http://www.zwyssig.info/license'>
          cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 Software License Agreement&#xA;NOTICE TO USER: PLEASE READ THIS AGREEMENT CAREFULLY. BY COPYING,&#xA;INSTALLING OR USING ALL OR ANY PORTION OF THE SOFTWARE YOU ACCEPT&#xA;ALL THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS AGREEMENT, INCLUDING, IN&#xA;PARTICULAR THE PROVISIONS ON: TRANSFERABILITY IN SECTION 4; WARRANTY&#xA;IN SECTIONS 6 AND 7; LIABILITY IN SECTION 8; CONNECTIVITY AND&#xA;PRIVACY IN SECTION 13; AND SPECIFIC PROVISIONS AND EXCEPTIONS&#xA;IN SECTION 14. YOU AGREE THAT THIS AGREEMENT IS LIKE ANY WRITTEN&#xA;NEGOTIATED AGREEMENT SIGNED BY YOU. THIS AGREEMENT IS ENFORCEABLE&#xA;AGAINST YOU AND ANY LEGAL ENTITY THAT OBTAINED THE SOFTWARE AND&#xA;ON WHOSE BEHALF IT IS USED: FOR EXAMPLE, IF APPLICABLE, YOUR&#xA;EMPLOYER. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS AGREEMENT,&#xA;DO NOT USE AND/OR BUY THE SOFTWARE.&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 AND ITS SUPPLIERS OWN ALL INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY IN&#xA;THE SOFTWARE. THE SOFTWARE IS LICENSED, NOT SOLD. cleonproject.deliverables.release_1&#xA;PERMITS YOU TO COPY, DOWNLOAD, INSTALL, USE, OR OTHERWISE BENEFIT&#xA;FROM THE FUNCTIONALITY OR INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY OF THE SOFTWARE&#xA;ONLY IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS AGREEMENT. USE OF SOME&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 AND SOME THIRD PARTY MATERIALS AND SERVICES INCLUDED&#xA;IN OR ACCESSED THROUGH THE SOFTWARE MAY BE SUBJECT TO OTHER TERMS&#xA;AND CONDITIONS TYPICALLY FOUND IN A SEPARATE LICENSE AGREEMENT,&#xA;TERMS OF USE OR “READ ME” FILE LOCATED WITHIN OR NEAR SUCH MATERIALS&#xA;AND SERVICES OR AT http://www.zwyssig.info.&#xA;THE SOFTWARE MAY CAUSE YOUR COMPUTER TO AUTOMATICALLY CONNECT&#xA;TO THE INTERNET. SEE SECTIONS 13 AND 14 FOR ADDITIONAL INFORMATION.&#xA;THE SOFTWARE MAY INCLUDE PRODUCT ACTIVATION AND OTHER TECHNOLOGY&#xA;DESIGNED TO PREVENT UNAUTHORIZED USE AND COPYING. THIS TECHNOLOGY&#xA;MAY CAUSE YOUR COMPUTER TO AUTOMATICALLY CONNECT TO THE INTERNET&#xA;AS DESCRIBED IN SECTION 13. ADDITIONALLY, ONCE CONNECTED, THE&#xA;SOFTWARE MAY TRANSMIT YOUR SERIAL NUMBER TO cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 AND IN&#xA;DOING SO MAY PREVENT USES OF THE SOFTWARE THAT ARE NOT PERMITTED.&#xA;VISIT http://www.cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.com FOR ADDITIONAL INFORMATION ABOUT&#xA;PRODUCT ACTIVATION.&#xA;1. Definitions.&#xA;“cleonproject.deliverables.release_1” means Zwyssig Informatik GmbH, &#xA;Switzerland.&#xA;“Computer” means a virtual or physical computer device that accepts&#xA;information in digital or similar form and manipulates it for&#xA;a specific result based on a sequence of instructions.&#xA;“Internal Network” means a private, proprietary network resource&#xA;accessible only by employees and individual contractors (i.e.,&#xA;temporary employees) of a specific corporation or similar business&#xA;entity. Internal Network does not include portions of the Internet&#xA;or any other network community open to the public, such as membership&#xA;or subscription driven groups, associations and similar organizations.&#xA;“Output File” means an output file you create with the Software.&#xA;“Permitted Number” means one (1) unless otherwise indicated under&#xA;a valid license (e.g., volume license) granted by cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.&#xA;“Software” means (a) all of the information with which this agreement&#xA;is provided, including but not limited to (i) cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 or&#xA;third party software files and other computer information; (ii)&#xA;sample files bundled with cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 software or obtained from&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 through a separate service; (iii) related explanatory&#xA;written materials and files (“Documentation”); and (b) any modified&#xA;versions and copies of, and upgrades, updates and additions to,&#xA;such information, provided to you by cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 at any time,&#xA;to the extent not provided under a separate agreement (collectively,&#xA;“Updates”).&#xA;2. Software License.&#xA;If you obtained the Software and any required serial number(s)&#xA;from cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 or one of its authorized licensees and as long&#xA;as you comply with the terms of this agreement, cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 grants&#xA;you a non-exclusive license to install and use the Software in&#xA;a manner consistent with its design and Documentation and as&#xA;further set forth below. See Section 14 for specific provisions&#xA;related to the use of certain products and components.&#xA;2.1 General Use. You may install and use one copy of the Software&#xA;on up to the Permitted Number of your compatible Computers as&#xA;long as, when required by the Software, you present a valid serial&#xA;number for each copy; and&#xA;2.2 Distribution from Server. You may copy an image of the Software&#xA;onto file server(s) within your Internal Network for the purpose&#xA;of downloading and installing the Software onto Computers within&#xA;the same Internal Network for use as permitted by Section 2.1;&#xA;and&#xA;2.3 Server Use. You may install the Software on Computer file&#xA;server(s) within your Internal Network only for use of the Software&#xA;initiated by an individual from a Computer within the same Internal&#xA;Network as permitted by Section 2.1. The total number of users&#xA;(not the concurrent number of users) able to use the Software&#xA;on such Computer file server(s) may not exceed the Permitted&#xA;Number. By way of example, the foregoing does not permit you&#xA;to install or access (either directly or through commands, data&#xA;or instructions) the Software: (i) from or to a Computer not&#xA;part of your Internal Network, (ii) for enabling web hosted workgroups&#xA;or services available to the public, (iii) by any individual&#xA;or entity to use, download, copy or otherwise benefit from the&#xA;functionality of the Software unless licensed to do so by cleonproject.deliverables.release_1,&#xA;(iv) as a component of a system, workflow or service accessible&#xA;by more than the Permitted Number of users, or (v) for operations&#xA;not initiated by an individual user (e.g., automated server processing);&#xA;and&#xA;2.4 Backup Copy. You may make a reasonable number of backup copies&#xA;of the Software, provided your backup copies are not installed&#xA;or used for other than archival purposes.&#xA;2.5 Sample Application Code. You may modify the source code form&#xA;of those portions of such software programs that are identified&#xA;as sample code, sample application code, or components (each,&#xA;“Sample Application Code”) in the accompanying Documentation&#xA;solely for the purposes of designing, developing and testing&#xA;applications developed using cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 software programs; provided,&#xA;however, you are permitted to copy and distribute the Sample&#xA;Application Code (modified or unmodified) only if all of the&#xA;following conditions are met: (1) you distribute the compiled&#xA;object Sample Application Code with your application; (2) you&#xA;do not include the Sample Application Code in any product or&#xA;application designed for software development; and (3) you do&#xA;not use the cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 name, logos or other cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 trademarks&#xA;to market your application. You agree to indemnify, hold harmless&#xA;and defend cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 from and against any loss, damage, claims&#xA;or lawsuits, including attorney’s fees, that arise or result&#xA;from the use or distribution of your application. You may be&#xA;granted additional rights to modify or distribute cleonproject.deliverables.release_1&#xA;software code within documentation relating to such code and/or&#xA;the Software or in a separate agreement between you and cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.&#xA;2.6 Tryout Software. The Software, or portions of the Software,&#xA;may be configured to allow trial or tryout for a limited period&#xA;of time or for a limited number of launches. You are not permitted&#xA;to use the Software in a manner inconsistent with its design&#xA;or Documentation. For example, you may not use the Software after&#xA;its tryout period has ended unless you input a valid serial number.&#xA;ACCESS TO ANY OUTPUT FILES CREATED WITH THE SOFTWARE USED ON&#xA;A TRYOUT OR TRIAL BASIS IS ENTIRELY AT YOUR OWN RISK.&#xA;3. Intellectual Property Ownership.&#xA;The Software and any authorized copies that you make are the&#xA;intellectual property of and are owned by cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 and its&#xA;suppliers. The structure, organization and code of the Software&#xA;are the valuable trade secrets and confidential information of&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 and its suppliers. The Software is protected by law,&#xA;including but not limited to the copyright laws of the Switzerland&#xA;and other countries, and by international treaty provisions.&#xA;Except as expressly stated herein, this agreement does not grant&#xA;you any intellectual property rights in the Software and all&#xA;rights not expressly granted are reserved by cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 and&#xA;its suppliers.&#xA;4. Restrictions and Requirements.&#xA;4.1 Notices. Any permitted copy of the Software that you make&#xA;must contain the same copyright and other proprietary notices&#xA;that appear on or in the Software.&#xA;4.2 Use Obligations. You agree that you will not use the Software&#xA;other than as permitted by this agreement and that you will not&#xA;use the Software in a manner inconsistent with its design or&#xA;Documentation.&#xA;4.3 No Modifications. Except as permitted in Section 14, you&#xA;may not modify, adapt or translate the Software.&#xA;4.4 No Reverse Engineering. You will not reverse engineer, decompile,&#xA;disassemble or otherwise attempt to discover the source code&#xA;of the Software except to the extent you may be expressly permitted&#xA;under applicable law to decompile only in order to achieve interoperability&#xA;with the Software.&#xA;4.5 No Unbundling. The Software may include various applications,&#xA;utilities and components, may support multiple platforms and&#xA;languages and may be provided to you on multiple media or in&#xA;multiple copies. Nonetheless, the Software is designed and provided&#xA;to you as a single product to be used as a single product on&#xA;Computers as permitted by Sections 2 and 14. You are not required&#xA;to install all component parts of the Software, but you may not&#xA;unbundle the component parts of the Software for use on different&#xA;Computers. You may not unbundle or repackage the Software for&#xA;distribution, transfer or resale. See Section 14 for specific&#xA;exceptions to this Section 4.5.&#xA;4.6 No Transfer. YOU WILL NOT RENT, LEASE, SELL, SUBLICENSE,&#xA;ASSIGN OR TRANSFER YOUR RIGHTS IN THE SOFTWARE, OR AUTHORIZE&#xA;ANY PORTION OF THE SOFTWARE TO BE COPIED ONTO ANOTHER INDIVIDUAL&#xA;OR LEGAL ENTITY’S COMPUTER EXCEPT AS MAY BE EXPRESSLY PERMITTED&#xA;HEREIN. You may, however, permanently transfer all your rights&#xA;to use the Software to another individual or legal entity provided&#xA;that: (a) you also transfer (i) this agreement, (ii) the serial&#xA;number(s), the Software affixed to media provided by cleonproject.deliverables.release_1&#xA;or its authorized distributor, and all other software or hardware&#xA;bundled, packaged or pre-installed with the Software, including&#xA;all copies, upgrades, updates and prior versions, to such individual&#xA;or entity; (b) you retain no upgrades, updates or copies, including&#xA;backups and copies stored on a Computer; and (c) the receiving&#xA;party accepts the terms and conditions of this agreement and&#xA;any other terms and conditions under which you purchased a valid&#xA;license to the Software. NOTWITHSTANDING THE FOREGOING, YOU MAY&#xA;NOT TRANSFER EDUCATION, PRERELEASE,&#xA;OR NOT FOR RESALE COPIES OF THE SOFTWARE. Prior to a transfer&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 may require that you and the receiving party confirm&#xA;in writing your compliance with this agreement, provide cleonproject.deliverables.release_1&#xA;with information about yourselves, and register as end-users&#xA;of the Software. Allow 4-6 weeks to&#xA;transfer. Please visit http://www.cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.com or contact&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 for more information.&#xA;4.7 No Service Bureau. You will not use or offer the Software&#xA;on a service bureau basis. By way of example, you are not allowed&#xA;to offer the Software as a service (SaaS).&#xA;5. Updates.&#xA;If the Software is an upgrade or update to a previous version&#xA;of cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 software, you must possess a valid license to&#xA;such previous version in order to use such upgrade or update.&#xA;After you install such update or upgrade, you may continue to&#xA;use any such previous version in accordance with its end-user&#xA;license agreement only if (a) the upgrade or update and all previous&#xA;versions are installed on the same Computer, (b) the previous&#xA;versions or copies thereof are not transferred to another party&#xA;or device unless all copies of the update or upgrade are also&#xA;transferred to such party or device and (c) you acknowledge that&#xA;any obligation cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 may have to support the previous version(s)&#xA;may end upon the availability of the upgrade or update. No other&#xA;use of the previous version(s) is permitted after installation&#xA;of an update or upgrade. Upgrades and updates may be licensed&#xA;to you by cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 with additional or different terms.&#xA;6. LIMITED WARRANTY.&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 warrants to the individual or entity that first purchases&#xA;a license for the Software for use pursuant to the terms of this&#xA;agreement that the Software will perform substantially in accordance&#xA;with the Documentation for the ninety (90) day period following&#xA;receipt of the Software when used on the recommended operating&#xA;system and hardware configuration. Non-substantial variation&#xA;of performance from the Documentation does not establish a warranty&#xA;right. This limited warranty does not apply to the following,&#xA;which are made available AS-IS and without warranty from cleonproject.deliverables.release_1:&#xA;patches, pre-release (beta), trial, starter, evaluation, product&#xA;sampler, and not for resale (NFR) copies of the Software; websites,&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 Online Services; Third Party Online Services; and&#xA;any software made available by cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 for free via web download&#xA;from an cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 website. All warranty claims must be made,&#xA;along with proof of purchase, to cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 within such ninety&#xA;(90) day period. Visit the cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 website at http://www.cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.com&#xA;for more information about warranty claims. If the Software does&#xA;not perform substantially in accordance with the Documentation,&#xA;the entire liability of cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 and its affiliates and your&#xA;exclusive remedy will be limited to either, at cleonproject.deliverables.release_1’s&#xA;option, replacement of the Software or refund of the license&#xA;fee you paid for the Software. THE LIMITED WARRANTY SET FORTH&#xA;IN THIS SECTION GIVES YOU SPECIFIC LEGAL RIGHTS. YOU MAY HAVE&#xA;ADDITIONAL RIGHTS UNDER LAW WHICH VARY FROM JURISDICTION TO JURISDICTION.&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 DOES NOT SEEK TO LIMIT YOUR WARRANTY RIGHTS TO ANY&#xA;EXTENT NOT PERMITTED BY LAW. Please see Section 14 for jurisdiction-specific&#xA;provisions or contact cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.&#xA;7. DISCLAIMER.&#xA;THE FOREGOING LIMITED WARRANTY IS THE ONLY WARRANTY OFFERED BY&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 AND ITS AFFILIATES AND IT STATES THE SOLE AND EXCLUSIVE&#xA;REMEDIES FOR cleonproject.deliverables.release_1’S, ITS AFFILIATES’ OR SUPPLIERS’ BREACH&#xA;OF THAT OFFERED WARRANTY. THE FOREGOING OFFERED WARRANTY AND&#xA;ANY STATUTORY WARRANTY AND REMEDY THAT CANNOT BE EXCLUDED OR&#xA;LIMITED UNDER LAW ARE THE ONLY WARRANTIES APPLICABLE TO THE SOFTWARE.&#xA;OTHER THAN THOSE OFFERED AND STATUTORY WARRANTIES AND REMEDIES,&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.release_1, ITS AFFILIATES, SUPPLIERS AND CERTIFICATE AUTHORITIES&#xA;(DEFINED BELOW) DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES, CONDITIONS, REPRESENTATIONS&#xA;AND TERMS, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, WHETHER BY STATUTE, COMMON LAW,&#xA;CUSTOM, USAGE OR OTHERWISE AS TO ANY MATTER, INCLUDING BUT NOT&#xA;LIMITED TO PERFORMANCE, SECURITY, NON-INFRINGEMENT OF THIRD PARTY&#xA;RIGHTS, INTEGRATION, MERCHANTABILITY, QUIET ENJOYMENT, SATISFACTORY&#xA;QUALITY AND FITNESS FOR ANY PARTICULAR PURPOSE. OTHER THAN SUCH&#xA;OFFERED AND STATUTORY WARRANTIES AND REMEDIES, cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 AND&#xA;ITS SUPPLIERS PROVIDE THE SOFTWARE AND ACCESS TO ANY WEBSITES,&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 OR THIRD PARTY ONLINE SERVICES AND CERTIFICATE AUTHORITY&#xA;SERVICES AS-IS AND WITH ALL FAULTS. THIS DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTY&#xA;MAY NOT BE VALID IN SOME STATES. YOU MAY HAVE ADDITIONAL WARRANTY&#xA;RIGHTS UNDER LAW WHICH MAY NOT BE WAIVED OR DISCLAIMED. cleonproject.deliverables.release_1&#xA;DOES NOT SEEK TO LIMIT YOUR WARRANTY RIGHTS TO ANY EXTENT NOT&#xA;PERMITTED BY LAW. The provisions of Sections 7 and Section 8&#xA;will survive the termination of this agreement, howsoever caused,&#xA;but this will not imply or create any continued right to use&#xA;the Software after termination of this agreement.&#xA;8. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY.&#xA;EXCEPT FOR THE EXCLUSIVE REMEDY OFFERED BY cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 ABOVE&#xA;AND ANY REMEDIES THAT CANNOT BE EXCLUDED OR LIMITED UNDER LAW,&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.release_1, ITS AFFILIATES, SUPPLIERS, OR CERTIFICATE AUTHORITIES&#xA;WILL NOT BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR ANY LOSS, DAMAGES, CLAIMS OR COSTS&#xA;WHATSOEVER INCLUDING ANY CONSEQUENTIAL, INDIRECT OR INCIDENTAL&#xA;DAMAGES, ANY LOST PROFITS OR LOST SAVINGS, ANY DAMAGES RESULTING&#xA;FROM BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, PERSONAL INJURY OR FAILURE TO MEET&#xA;ANY DUTY OF CARE, OR CLAIMS BY A THIRD PARTY, EVEN IF AN cleonproject.deliverables.release_1&#xA;REPRESENTATIVE HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH LOSS,&#xA;DAMAGES, CLAIMS OR COSTS. IN ANY EVENT, cleonproject.deliverables.release_1’S AGGREGATE&#xA;LIABILITY AND THAT OF ITS AFFILIATES, SUPPLIERS, AND CERTIFICATE&#xA;AUTHORITIES UNDER OR IN CONNECTION WITH THIS AGREEMENT WILL BE&#xA;LIMITED TO THE AMOUNT PAID FOR THE SOFTWARE, IF ANY. THIS LIMITATION&#xA;WILL APPLY EVEN IN THE EVENT OF A FUNDAMENTAL OR MATERIAL BREACH&#xA;OR A BREACH OF THE FUNDAMENTAL OR MATERIAL TERMS OF THIS AGREEMENT.&#xA;Nothing contained in this agreement limits cleonproject.deliverables.release_1’s liability&#xA;to you in the event of death or personal injury resulting from&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.release_1’s negligence or for the tort of deceit (fraud). cleonproject.deliverables.release_1&#xA;is acting on behalf of its affiliates, suppliers, and Certificate&#xA;Authorities for the purpose of disclaiming, excluding and limiting&#xA;obligations, warranties and liability, but in no other respects&#xA;and for no other purpose. For further information, contact cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.&#xA;THE FOREGOING LIMITATIONS AND EXCLUSIONS APPLY TO THE EXTENT&#xA;PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW IN YOUR JURISDICTION. THIS LIMITATION&#xA;OF LIABILITY MAY NOT BE VALID IN SOME COUNTRIES. YOU MAY HAVE&#xA;RIGHTS THAT CANNOT BE WAIVED UNDER CONSUMER PROTECTION AND OTHER&#xA;LAWS. cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 DOES NOT SEEK TO LIMIT YOUR WARRANTY OR REMEDIES&#xA;TO ANY EXTENT NOT PERMITTED BY LAW. SEE SECTION 14 FOR JURISDICTION-SPECIFIC&#xA;STATEMENTS.&#xA;9. Export Rules.&#xA;You agree that the Software will not be shipped, transferred&#xA;or exported into any country or used in any manner prohibited&#xA;by the United States Export Administration Act or any other export&#xA;laws, restrictions or regulations (collectively the “Export Laws”).&#xA;In addition, if the Software is identified as an export controlled&#xA;item under the Export Laws, you represent and warrant that you&#xA;are not a citizen of, or located within, an embargoed or otherwise&#xA;restricted nation  and that you are not otherwise prohibited&#xA;under the Export Laws from receiving the Software. All rights&#xA;to use the Software are granted on condition that such rights&#xA;are forfeited if you fail to comply with the terms of this agreement.&#xA;10. Governing Law.&#xA;If you are a consumer who uses the Software for only personal&#xA;non-business purposes, then this agreement will be governed by&#xA;the laws of the state in which you purchased the license to use&#xA;the Software. If you are not such a consumer, this agreement&#xA;will be governed by and construed in accordance with the substantive&#xA;laws in force in SWITZERLAND. The commercial court of the canton&#xA;of Aargau shall have non-exclusive jurisdiction over all disputes&#xA;relating to this agreement. This agreement will not be governed&#xA;by the conflict of law rules of any jurisdiction or the United&#xA;Nations Convention on Contracts for the International Sale of&#xA;Goods, the application of which is expressly excluded.&#xA;11. General Provisions.&#xA;If any part of this agreement is found void and unenforceable,&#xA;it will not affect the validity of the balance of this agreement,&#xA;which will remain valid and enforceable according to its terms&#xA;This agreement may only be modified in writing, signed by an&#xA;authorized officer of cleonproject.deliverables.release_1. This is the entire agreement&#xA;between cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 and you relating to the Software and it supersedes&#xA;any prior representations, discussions, undertakings, communications&#xA;or advertising relating to the Software.&#xA;12. Compliance with Licenses.&#xA;If you are a business, company, or organization, you agree that,&#xA;no more than once every 12 months, cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 or its authorized&#xA;representative shall, upon 10 days’ prior notice to you, have&#xA;the right to inspect your records, systems, and facilities to&#xA;verify that your use of any and all cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 software is in&#xA;conformity with your valid licenses from cleonproject.deliverables.release_1. If a verification&#xA;discloses that your use is not in conformity with a valid license,&#xA;you shall immediately obtain valid licenses to bring your use&#xA;into conformity.&#xA;13. Internet Connectivity and Privacy.&#xA;13.1 Automatic Connections to the Internet.&#xA;The Software may cause your Computer to automatically connect&#xA;to the Internet and to communicate with an cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 website&#xA;for purposes that may include providing you with additional information,&#xA;features and functionality. The following provisions apply to&#xA;all automatic Internet connections by the Software:&#xA;13.1.1 When the Software automatically connects to the Internet,&#xA;an Internet protocol address (“IP Address”) that is associated&#xA;with your current Internet connection is sent to an cleonproject.deliverables.release_1&#xA;website;&#xA;13.1.2 When the Software automatically connects to the Internet,&#xA;no personally identifiable information is sent except to the&#xA;extent that IP Addresses may be considered personally identifiable&#xA;in some jurisdictions; and&#xA;13.1.3 Whenever the Software makes an Internet connection and&#xA;communicates with an cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 website, unless you are provided&#xA;with separate terms of use at that time, the cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.com&#xA;Terms of Use (http://www.cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.com) shall apply. Please&#xA;note that the cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 Privacy Policy allows tracking of website&#xA;visits and it addresses in detail the topic of tracking and use&#xA;of cookies, web beacons and similar devices.&#xA;13.1.4 The Software may transmit your serial number and your&#xA;e-mail address you used to register your license to cleonproject.deliverables.release_1&#xA;and in doing so may prevent uses of the Software that are not&#xA;permitted.&#xA;13.2 Updating. The Software may cause your Computer to automatically&#xA;connect to the Internet to check for Updates that are available&#xA;for automatic download to your Computer and to let cleonproject.deliverables.release_1&#xA;know the Software is successfully installed. Please consult the&#xA;Documentation for information about changing default update settings.&#xA;13.4 Use of cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 Online Services. The Software may use&#xA;your Computer to automatically connect to the Internet to facilitate&#xA;your access to content and services that are provided to you&#xA;by cleonproject.deliverables.release_1. Your Software may automatically update downloadable&#xA;materials from these services so as to provide immediate availability&#xA;of these services even when you are offline. Please consult the&#xA;Documentation for information about changing default update settings.&#xA;13.5 Digital Certificates. The Software uses digital certificates&#xA;to help you identify downloaded files (e.g., applications and&#xA;content) and the publishers of those files. Your Computer may&#xA;connect to the Internet at the time of validation of a digital&#xA;certificate.&#xA;14. Specific Provisions and Exceptions.&#xA;This section sets forth specific provisions related to certain&#xA;products and components of the Software as well as limited exceptions&#xA;to the above terms and conditions. To the extent that any provision&#xA;in this section is in conflict with any other term or condition&#xA;in this agreement, this section will supersede such other term&#xA;or condition.&#xA;14.1 No Prejudice, European Union Provisions.&#xA;14.1.1 This agreement will not prejudice the statutory rights&#xA;of any party, including those dealing as consumers. For example,&#xA;for consumers in New Zealand who obtain the Software for personal,&#xA;domestic or household use (not business purposes), this agreement&#xA;is subject to the Consumer Guarantees Act.&#xA;14.1.2 If you obtained the Software in the European Union (EU),&#xA;you usually reside in the EU and you are a consumer (that is&#xA;you use the Software for personal, non-business related purposes),&#xA;then Section 6 does not apply to your purchase and use of the&#xA;Software. Instead, cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 warrants for a period of 2 years&#xA;from purchase that the Software provides the functionalities&#xA;set forth in the Documentation (the “agreed upon functionalities”)&#xA;when used on the recommended hardware configuration. Non-substantial&#xA;variation from the agreed upon functionalities will not establish&#xA;any warranty rights. THIS WARRANTY DOES NOT APPLY TO SOFTWARE&#xA;THAT YOU REQUEST TO USE ON A PRE-RELEASE, TRYOUT, STARTER, PRODUCT&#xA;SAMPLER BASIS, OR TO FONT SOFTWARE CONVERTED INTO OTHER FORMATS&#xA;OR TO THE EXTENT THE SOFTWARE FAILS TO PERFORM BECAUSE IT HAS&#xA;BEEN ALTERED BY YOU. To make a warranty claim, you must notify&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 during this 2 year period, providing details of proof&#xA;of purchase of the Software. cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 will verify with you&#xA;whether there is a defect in the Software or advise you that&#xA;the error arises because you have not installed the Software&#xA;correctly (in which case, cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 shall assist you). If there&#xA;is a defect in the Software, you may request from cleonproject.deliverables.release_1&#xA;either a refund or a repaired/replacement copy of the Software.&#xA;Requests must be accompanied by proof of purchase. In the event&#xA;your warranty details are substantiated, cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 will meet&#xA;your request for repaired/replacement Software, unless it is&#xA;not reasonable for cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 to do so, in which case cleonproject.deliverables.release_1&#xA;will provide you with a refund. For warranty assistance, please&#xA;contact cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.&#xA;Please note that the provisions of Section 8 (Limitation of Liability)&#xA;will continue to apply to any damages claims you make in respect&#xA;of your use of the Software. Nonetheless, cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 shall be&#xA;liable for direct losses that are reasonably foreseeable in the&#xA;event of a breach by cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 of this agreement. You are advised&#xA;to take all reasonable measures to avoid and reduce damages,&#xA;in particular by making back-up copies of the Software and your&#xA;computer data.&#xA;This agreement, and in particular, this Section 14.1.2, is intended&#xA;to describe your rights (including your statutory rights) in&#xA;the event there should be problems with your use of the Software.&#xA;If your statutory rights should be greater than this description,&#xA;your statutory rights shall apply.&#xA;14.2 Pre-release Software Additional Terms. If the Software is&#xA;pre-commercial release or beta software (“Pre-release Software”),&#xA;then this section applies. The Pre-release Software is a pre-release&#xA;version, does not represent final product from cleonproject.deliverables.release_1, and&#xA;may contain bugs, errors and other problems that could cause&#xA;system or other failures and data loss. cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 may never&#xA;commercially release the Pre-release Software. If you received&#xA;the Pre-release Software pursuant to a separate written agreement&#xA;your use of the Software is also governed by such agreement.&#xA;You will return or destroy all copies of Pre-release Software&#xA;upon request by cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 or upon cleonproject.deliverables.release_1’s commercial&#xA;release of such Software. YOUR USE OF PRE-RELEASE SOFTWARE IS&#xA;AT YOUR OWN RISK. SEE SECTIONS 7 AND 8 FOR WARRANTY DISCLAIMERS&#xA;AND LIABILITY LIMITATIONS WHICH GOVERN PRE-RELEASE SOFTWARE.&#xA;If you have any questions regarding this agreement or if you&#xA;wish to request any information from cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 please use the&#xA;address and contact information included with this product to&#xA;contact cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 is a registered trademark of cleonproject.deliverables.release_1 in the Switzerland&#xA;and/or other countries. All other trademarks are the property&#xA;of their respective owners.
        </license>
      </licenses>
      <copyright uri='http://www.zwyssig.info/copyright' url='http://www.zwyssig.info/copyright'>
        Zwyssig Informatik GmbH
      </copyright>
    </unit>
    <unit id='cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.model.project.builtin' version='0.2.2'>
      <update id='cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.model.project.builtin' range='[0.0.0,0.2.2)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='1'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.model.project'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='5'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.model.project.builtin' version='0.2.2'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.model.project.builtin' version='0.2.2'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.model.project' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.model.project.javamodel' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='bundle' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='21'>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='ch.actifsource.core' range='9.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='ch.actifsource.environment' range='9.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='ch.actifsource.util' range='9.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='ch.actifsource.xml' range='9.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='ch.actifsource.template' range='9.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='ch.actifsource.ui.wizard.generic' range='9.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='ch.actifsource.ui.wizard' range='9.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.eclipse.core.runtime' range='3.13.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.common.doc.template.asciidoc.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.initialization.projectmanagement.spec.steering.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.initialization.projectmanagement.spec.projectmanagement.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.common.doc.spec.doc.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.common.resources.spec.resources.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.initialization.projectmanagement.spec.planning.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.initialization.projectmanagement.spec.resource.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.initialization.projectmanagement.model.hermes.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.common.resources.spec.calendar.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.initialization.projectmanagement.spec.hermes.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.common.importwizard.template.java.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='cleon.common.importwizard.spec.xml2asrc.builtin' range='0.3.27'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='ch.actifsource.generator' range='9.0.0'/>
      </requires>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.model.project.builtin' version='0.2.2'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-SymbolicName: cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.model.project.builtin;singleton:=true&#xA;Bundle-Version: 0.2.2
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
    <unit id='deliverables' version='1.0.0.07777dJlHvE'>
      <properties size='2'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='Deliverables'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.type.category' value='true'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='1'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='deliverables' version='1.0.0.07777dJlHvE'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='2'>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleonproject.deliverables.release_1.feature.group' range='[0.2.2,0.2.2]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.feature.group' range='[0.2.2,0.2.2]'/>
      </requires>
      <touchpoint id='null' version='0.0.0'/>
    </unit>
    <unit id='cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.feature.jar' version='0.2.2'>
      <properties size='3'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='cleonproject.deliverables.architecture'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='No description available'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description.url' value='http://www.zwyssig.info/description'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='3'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.feature.jar' version='0.2.2'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='feature' version='1.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.update.feature' name='cleonproject.deliverables.architecture' version='0.2.2'/>
      </provides>
      <filter>
        (org.eclipse.update.install.features=true)
      </filter>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='org.eclipse.update.feature' id='cleonproject.deliverables.architecture' version='0.2.2'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='zipped'>
            true
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
      <licenses size='1'>
        <license uri='http://www.zwyssig.info/license' url='http://www.zwyssig.info/license'>
          cleonproject.deliverables.architecture Software License Agreement&#xA;NOTICE TO USER: PLEASE READ THIS AGREEMENT CAREFULLY. BY COPYING,&#xA;INSTALLING OR USING ALL OR ANY PORTION OF THE SOFTWARE YOU ACCEPT&#xA;ALL THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS AGREEMENT, INCLUDING, IN&#xA;PARTICULAR THE PROVISIONS ON: TRANSFERABILITY IN SECTION 4; WARRANTY&#xA;IN SECTIONS 6 AND 7; LIABILITY IN SECTION 8; CONNECTIVITY AND&#xA;PRIVACY IN SECTION 13; AND SPECIFIC PROVISIONS AND EXCEPTIONS&#xA;IN SECTION 14. YOU AGREE THAT THIS AGREEMENT IS LIKE ANY WRITTEN&#xA;NEGOTIATED AGREEMENT SIGNED BY YOU. THIS AGREEMENT IS ENFORCEABLE&#xA;AGAINST YOU AND ANY LEGAL ENTITY THAT OBTAINED THE SOFTWARE AND&#xA;ON WHOSE BEHALF IT IS USED: FOR EXAMPLE, IF APPLICABLE, YOUR&#xA;EMPLOYER. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS AGREEMENT,&#xA;DO NOT USE AND/OR BUY THE SOFTWARE.&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.architecture AND ITS SUPPLIERS OWN ALL INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY IN&#xA;THE SOFTWARE. THE SOFTWARE IS LICENSED, NOT SOLD. cleonproject.deliverables.architecture&#xA;PERMITS YOU TO COPY, DOWNLOAD, INSTALL, USE, OR OTHERWISE BENEFIT&#xA;FROM THE FUNCTIONALITY OR INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY OF THE SOFTWARE&#xA;ONLY IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS AGREEMENT. USE OF SOME&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.architecture AND SOME THIRD PARTY MATERIALS AND SERVICES INCLUDED&#xA;IN OR ACCESSED THROUGH THE SOFTWARE MAY BE SUBJECT TO OTHER TERMS&#xA;AND CONDITIONS TYPICALLY FOUND IN A SEPARATE LICENSE AGREEMENT,&#xA;TERMS OF USE OR “READ ME” FILE LOCATED WITHIN OR NEAR SUCH MATERIALS&#xA;AND SERVICES OR AT http://www.zwyssig.info.&#xA;THE SOFTWARE MAY CAUSE YOUR COMPUTER TO AUTOMATICALLY CONNECT&#xA;TO THE INTERNET. SEE SECTIONS 13 AND 14 FOR ADDITIONAL INFORMATION.&#xA;THE SOFTWARE MAY INCLUDE PRODUCT ACTIVATION AND OTHER TECHNOLOGY&#xA;DESIGNED TO PREVENT UNAUTHORIZED USE AND COPYING. THIS TECHNOLOGY&#xA;MAY CAUSE YOUR COMPUTER TO AUTOMATICALLY CONNECT TO THE INTERNET&#xA;AS DESCRIBED IN SECTION 13. ADDITIONALLY, ONCE CONNECTED, THE&#xA;SOFTWARE MAY TRANSMIT YOUR SERIAL NUMBER TO cleonproject.deliverables.architecture AND IN&#xA;DOING SO MAY PREVENT USES OF THE SOFTWARE THAT ARE NOT PERMITTED.&#xA;VISIT http://www.cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.com FOR ADDITIONAL INFORMATION ABOUT&#xA;PRODUCT ACTIVATION.&#xA;1. Definitions.&#xA;“cleonproject.deliverables.architecture” means Zwyssig Informatik GmbH, &#xA;Switzerland.&#xA;“Computer” means a virtual or physical computer device that accepts&#xA;information in digital or similar form and manipulates it for&#xA;a specific result based on a sequence of instructions.&#xA;“Internal Network” means a private, proprietary network resource&#xA;accessible only by employees and individual contractors (i.e.,&#xA;temporary employees) of a specific corporation or similar business&#xA;entity. Internal Network does not include portions of the Internet&#xA;or any other network community open to the public, such as membership&#xA;or subscription driven groups, associations and similar organizations.&#xA;“Output File” means an output file you create with the Software.&#xA;“Permitted Number” means one (1) unless otherwise indicated under&#xA;a valid license (e.g., volume license) granted by cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.&#xA;“Software” means (a) all of the information with which this agreement&#xA;is provided, including but not limited to (i) cleonproject.deliverables.architecture or&#xA;third party software files and other computer information; (ii)&#xA;sample files bundled with cleonproject.deliverables.architecture software or obtained from&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.architecture through a separate service; (iii) related explanatory&#xA;written materials and files (“Documentation”); and (b) any modified&#xA;versions and copies of, and upgrades, updates and additions to,&#xA;such information, provided to you by cleonproject.deliverables.architecture at any time,&#xA;to the extent not provided under a separate agreement (collectively,&#xA;“Updates”).&#xA;2. Software License.&#xA;If you obtained the Software and any required serial number(s)&#xA;from cleonproject.deliverables.architecture or one of its authorized licensees and as long&#xA;as you comply with the terms of this agreement, cleonproject.deliverables.architecture grants&#xA;you a non-exclusive license to install and use the Software in&#xA;a manner consistent with its design and Documentation and as&#xA;further set forth below. See Section 14 for specific provisions&#xA;related to the use of certain products and components.&#xA;2.1 General Use. You may install and use one copy of the Software&#xA;on up to the Permitted Number of your compatible Computers as&#xA;long as, when required by the Software, you present a valid serial&#xA;number for each copy; and&#xA;2.2 Distribution from Server. You may copy an image of the Software&#xA;onto file server(s) within your Internal Network for the purpose&#xA;of downloading and installing the Software onto Computers within&#xA;the same Internal Network for use as permitted by Section 2.1;&#xA;and&#xA;2.3 Server Use. You may install the Software on Computer file&#xA;server(s) within your Internal Network only for use of the Software&#xA;initiated by an individual from a Computer within the same Internal&#xA;Network as permitted by Section 2.1. The total number of users&#xA;(not the concurrent number of users) able to use the Software&#xA;on such Computer file server(s) may not exceed the Permitted&#xA;Number. By way of example, the foregoing does not permit you&#xA;to install or access (either directly or through commands, data&#xA;or instructions) the Software: (i) from or to a Computer not&#xA;part of your Internal Network, (ii) for enabling web hosted workgroups&#xA;or services available to the public, (iii) by any individual&#xA;or entity to use, download, copy or otherwise benefit from the&#xA;functionality of the Software unless licensed to do so by cleonproject.deliverables.architecture,&#xA;(iv) as a component of a system, workflow or service accessible&#xA;by more than the Permitted Number of users, or (v) for operations&#xA;not initiated by an individual user (e.g., automated server processing);&#xA;and&#xA;2.4 Backup Copy. You may make a reasonable number of backup copies&#xA;of the Software, provided your backup copies are not installed&#xA;or used for other than archival purposes.&#xA;2.5 Sample Application Code. You may modify the source code form&#xA;of those portions of such software programs that are identified&#xA;as sample code, sample application code, or components (each,&#xA;“Sample Application Code”) in the accompanying Documentation&#xA;solely for the purposes of designing, developing and testing&#xA;applications developed using cleonproject.deliverables.architecture software programs; provided,&#xA;however, you are permitted to copy and distribute the Sample&#xA;Application Code (modified or unmodified) only if all of the&#xA;following conditions are met: (1) you distribute the compiled&#xA;object Sample Application Code with your application; (2) you&#xA;do not include the Sample Application Code in any product or&#xA;application designed for software development; and (3) you do&#xA;not use the cleonproject.deliverables.architecture name, logos or other cleonproject.deliverables.architecture trademarks&#xA;to market your application. You agree to indemnify, hold harmless&#xA;and defend cleonproject.deliverables.architecture from and against any loss, damage, claims&#xA;or lawsuits, including attorney’s fees, that arise or result&#xA;from the use or distribution of your application. You may be&#xA;granted additional rights to modify or distribute cleonproject.deliverables.architecture&#xA;software code within documentation relating to such code and/or&#xA;the Software or in a separate agreement between you and cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.&#xA;2.6 Tryout Software. The Software, or portions of the Software,&#xA;may be configured to allow trial or tryout for a limited period&#xA;of time or for a limited number of launches. You are not permitted&#xA;to use the Software in a manner inconsistent with its design&#xA;or Documentation. For example, you may not use the Software after&#xA;its tryout period has ended unless you input a valid serial number.&#xA;ACCESS TO ANY OUTPUT FILES CREATED WITH THE SOFTWARE USED ON&#xA;A TRYOUT OR TRIAL BASIS IS ENTIRELY AT YOUR OWN RISK.&#xA;3. Intellectual Property Ownership.&#xA;The Software and any authorized copies that you make are the&#xA;intellectual property of and are owned by cleonproject.deliverables.architecture and its&#xA;suppliers. The structure, organization and code of the Software&#xA;are the valuable trade secrets and confidential information of&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.architecture and its suppliers. The Software is protected by law,&#xA;including but not limited to the copyright laws of the Switzerland&#xA;and other countries, and by international treaty provisions.&#xA;Except as expressly stated herein, this agreement does not grant&#xA;you any intellectual property rights in the Software and all&#xA;rights not expressly granted are reserved by cleonproject.deliverables.architecture and&#xA;its suppliers.&#xA;4. Restrictions and Requirements.&#xA;4.1 Notices. Any permitted copy of the Software that you make&#xA;must contain the same copyright and other proprietary notices&#xA;that appear on or in the Software.&#xA;4.2 Use Obligations. You agree that you will not use the Software&#xA;other than as permitted by this agreement and that you will not&#xA;use the Software in a manner inconsistent with its design or&#xA;Documentation.&#xA;4.3 No Modifications. Except as permitted in Section 14, you&#xA;may not modify, adapt or translate the Software.&#xA;4.4 No Reverse Engineering. You will not reverse engineer, decompile,&#xA;disassemble or otherwise attempt to discover the source code&#xA;of the Software except to the extent you may be expressly permitted&#xA;under applicable law to decompile only in order to achieve interoperability&#xA;with the Software.&#xA;4.5 No Unbundling. The Software may include various applications,&#xA;utilities and components, may support multiple platforms and&#xA;languages and may be provided to you on multiple media or in&#xA;multiple copies. Nonetheless, the Software is designed and provided&#xA;to you as a single product to be used as a single product on&#xA;Computers as permitted by Sections 2 and 14. You are not required&#xA;to install all component parts of the Software, but you may not&#xA;unbundle the component parts of the Software for use on different&#xA;Computers. You may not unbundle or repackage the Software for&#xA;distribution, transfer or resale. See Section 14 for specific&#xA;exceptions to this Section 4.5.&#xA;4.6 No Transfer. YOU WILL NOT RENT, LEASE, SELL, SUBLICENSE,&#xA;ASSIGN OR TRANSFER YOUR RIGHTS IN THE SOFTWARE, OR AUTHORIZE&#xA;ANY PORTION OF THE SOFTWARE TO BE COPIED ONTO ANOTHER INDIVIDUAL&#xA;OR LEGAL ENTITY’S COMPUTER EXCEPT AS MAY BE EXPRESSLY PERMITTED&#xA;HEREIN. You may, however, permanently transfer all your rights&#xA;to use the Software to another individual or legal entity provided&#xA;that: (a) you also transfer (i) this agreement, (ii) the serial&#xA;number(s), the Software affixed to media provided by cleonproject.deliverables.architecture&#xA;or its authorized distributor, and all other software or hardware&#xA;bundled, packaged or pre-installed with the Software, including&#xA;all copies, upgrades, updates and prior versions, to such individual&#xA;or entity; (b) you retain no upgrades, updates or copies, including&#xA;backups and copies stored on a Computer; and (c) the receiving&#xA;party accepts the terms and conditions of this agreement and&#xA;any other terms and conditions under which you purchased a valid&#xA;license to the Software. NOTWITHSTANDING THE FOREGOING, YOU MAY&#xA;NOT TRANSFER EDUCATION, PRERELEASE,&#xA;OR NOT FOR RESALE COPIES OF THE SOFTWARE. Prior to a transfer&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.architecture may require that you and the receiving party confirm&#xA;in writing your compliance with this agreement, provide cleonproject.deliverables.architecture&#xA;with information about yourselves, and register as end-users&#xA;of the Software. Allow 4-6 weeks to&#xA;transfer. Please visit http://www.cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.com or contact&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.architecture for more information.&#xA;4.7 No Service Bureau. You will not use or offer the Software&#xA;on a service bureau basis. By way of example, you are not allowed&#xA;to offer the Software as a service (SaaS).&#xA;5. Updates.&#xA;If the Software is an upgrade or update to a previous version&#xA;of cleonproject.deliverables.architecture software, you must possess a valid license to&#xA;such previous version in order to use such upgrade or update.&#xA;After you install such update or upgrade, you may continue to&#xA;use any such previous version in accordance with its end-user&#xA;license agreement only if (a) the upgrade or update and all previous&#xA;versions are installed on the same Computer, (b) the previous&#xA;versions or copies thereof are not transferred to another party&#xA;or device unless all copies of the update or upgrade are also&#xA;transferred to such party or device and (c) you acknowledge that&#xA;any obligation cleonproject.deliverables.architecture may have to support the previous version(s)&#xA;may end upon the availability of the upgrade or update. No other&#xA;use of the previous version(s) is permitted after installation&#xA;of an update or upgrade. Upgrades and updates may be licensed&#xA;to you by cleonproject.deliverables.architecture with additional or different terms.&#xA;6. LIMITED WARRANTY.&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.architecture warrants to the individual or entity that first purchases&#xA;a license for the Software for use pursuant to the terms of this&#xA;agreement that the Software will perform substantially in accordance&#xA;with the Documentation for the ninety (90) day period following&#xA;receipt of the Software when used on the recommended operating&#xA;system and hardware configuration. Non-substantial variation&#xA;of performance from the Documentation does not establish a warranty&#xA;right. This limited warranty does not apply to the following,&#xA;which are made available AS-IS and without warranty from cleonproject.deliverables.architecture:&#xA;patches, pre-release (beta), trial, starter, evaluation, product&#xA;sampler, and not for resale (NFR) copies of the Software; websites,&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.architecture Online Services; Third Party Online Services; and&#xA;any software made available by cleonproject.deliverables.architecture for free via web download&#xA;from an cleonproject.deliverables.architecture website. All warranty claims must be made,&#xA;along with proof of purchase, to cleonproject.deliverables.architecture within such ninety&#xA;(90) day period. Visit the cleonproject.deliverables.architecture website at http://www.cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.com&#xA;for more information about warranty claims. If the Software does&#xA;not perform substantially in accordance with the Documentation,&#xA;the entire liability of cleonproject.deliverables.architecture and its affiliates and your&#xA;exclusive remedy will be limited to either, at cleonproject.deliverables.architecture’s&#xA;option, replacement of the Software or refund of the license&#xA;fee you paid for the Software. THE LIMITED WARRANTY SET FORTH&#xA;IN THIS SECTION GIVES YOU SPECIFIC LEGAL RIGHTS. YOU MAY HAVE&#xA;ADDITIONAL RIGHTS UNDER LAW WHICH VARY FROM JURISDICTION TO JURISDICTION.&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.architecture DOES NOT SEEK TO LIMIT YOUR WARRANTY RIGHTS TO ANY&#xA;EXTENT NOT PERMITTED BY LAW. Please see Section 14 for jurisdiction-specific&#xA;provisions or contact cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.&#xA;7. DISCLAIMER.&#xA;THE FOREGOING LIMITED WARRANTY IS THE ONLY WARRANTY OFFERED BY&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.architecture AND ITS AFFILIATES AND IT STATES THE SOLE AND EXCLUSIVE&#xA;REMEDIES FOR cleonproject.deliverables.architecture’S, ITS AFFILIATES’ OR SUPPLIERS’ BREACH&#xA;OF THAT OFFERED WARRANTY. THE FOREGOING OFFERED WARRANTY AND&#xA;ANY STATUTORY WARRANTY AND REMEDY THAT CANNOT BE EXCLUDED OR&#xA;LIMITED UNDER LAW ARE THE ONLY WARRANTIES APPLICABLE TO THE SOFTWARE.&#xA;OTHER THAN THOSE OFFERED AND STATUTORY WARRANTIES AND REMEDIES,&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.architecture, ITS AFFILIATES, SUPPLIERS AND CERTIFICATE AUTHORITIES&#xA;(DEFINED BELOW) DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES, CONDITIONS, REPRESENTATIONS&#xA;AND TERMS, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, WHETHER BY STATUTE, COMMON LAW,&#xA;CUSTOM, USAGE OR OTHERWISE AS TO ANY MATTER, INCLUDING BUT NOT&#xA;LIMITED TO PERFORMANCE, SECURITY, NON-INFRINGEMENT OF THIRD PARTY&#xA;RIGHTS, INTEGRATION, MERCHANTABILITY, QUIET ENJOYMENT, SATISFACTORY&#xA;QUALITY AND FITNESS FOR ANY PARTICULAR PURPOSE. OTHER THAN SUCH&#xA;OFFERED AND STATUTORY WARRANTIES AND REMEDIES, cleonproject.deliverables.architecture AND&#xA;ITS SUPPLIERS PROVIDE THE SOFTWARE AND ACCESS TO ANY WEBSITES,&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.architecture OR THIRD PARTY ONLINE SERVICES AND CERTIFICATE AUTHORITY&#xA;SERVICES AS-IS AND WITH ALL FAULTS. THIS DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTY&#xA;MAY NOT BE VALID IN SOME STATES. YOU MAY HAVE ADDITIONAL WARRANTY&#xA;RIGHTS UNDER LAW WHICH MAY NOT BE WAIVED OR DISCLAIMED. cleonproject.deliverables.architecture&#xA;DOES NOT SEEK TO LIMIT YOUR WARRANTY RIGHTS TO ANY EXTENT NOT&#xA;PERMITTED BY LAW. The provisions of Sections 7 and Section 8&#xA;will survive the termination of this agreement, howsoever caused,&#xA;but this will not imply or create any continued right to use&#xA;the Software after termination of this agreement.&#xA;8. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY.&#xA;EXCEPT FOR THE EXCLUSIVE REMEDY OFFERED BY cleonproject.deliverables.architecture ABOVE&#xA;AND ANY REMEDIES THAT CANNOT BE EXCLUDED OR LIMITED UNDER LAW,&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.architecture, ITS AFFILIATES, SUPPLIERS, OR CERTIFICATE AUTHORITIES&#xA;WILL NOT BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR ANY LOSS, DAMAGES, CLAIMS OR COSTS&#xA;WHATSOEVER INCLUDING ANY CONSEQUENTIAL, INDIRECT OR INCIDENTAL&#xA;DAMAGES, ANY LOST PROFITS OR LOST SAVINGS, ANY DAMAGES RESULTING&#xA;FROM BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, PERSONAL INJURY OR FAILURE TO MEET&#xA;ANY DUTY OF CARE, OR CLAIMS BY A THIRD PARTY, EVEN IF AN cleonproject.deliverables.architecture&#xA;REPRESENTATIVE HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH LOSS,&#xA;DAMAGES, CLAIMS OR COSTS. IN ANY EVENT, cleonproject.deliverables.architecture’S AGGREGATE&#xA;LIABILITY AND THAT OF ITS AFFILIATES, SUPPLIERS, AND CERTIFICATE&#xA;AUTHORITIES UNDER OR IN CONNECTION WITH THIS AGREEMENT WILL BE&#xA;LIMITED TO THE AMOUNT PAID FOR THE SOFTWARE, IF ANY. THIS LIMITATION&#xA;WILL APPLY EVEN IN THE EVENT OF A FUNDAMENTAL OR MATERIAL BREACH&#xA;OR A BREACH OF THE FUNDAMENTAL OR MATERIAL TERMS OF THIS AGREEMENT.&#xA;Nothing contained in this agreement limits cleonproject.deliverables.architecture’s liability&#xA;to you in the event of death or personal injury resulting from&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.architecture’s negligence or for the tort of deceit (fraud). cleonproject.deliverables.architecture&#xA;is acting on behalf of its affiliates, suppliers, and Certificate&#xA;Authorities for the purpose of disclaiming, excluding and limiting&#xA;obligations, warranties and liability, but in no other respects&#xA;and for no other purpose. For further information, contact cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.&#xA;THE FOREGOING LIMITATIONS AND EXCLUSIONS APPLY TO THE EXTENT&#xA;PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW IN YOUR JURISDICTION. THIS LIMITATION&#xA;OF LIABILITY MAY NOT BE VALID IN SOME COUNTRIES. YOU MAY HAVE&#xA;RIGHTS THAT CANNOT BE WAIVED UNDER CONSUMER PROTECTION AND OTHER&#xA;LAWS. cleonproject.deliverables.architecture DOES NOT SEEK TO LIMIT YOUR WARRANTY OR REMEDIES&#xA;TO ANY EXTENT NOT PERMITTED BY LAW. SEE SECTION 14 FOR JURISDICTION-SPECIFIC&#xA;STATEMENTS.&#xA;9. Export Rules.&#xA;You agree that the Software will not be shipped, transferred&#xA;or exported into any country or used in any manner prohibited&#xA;by the United States Export Administration Act or any other export&#xA;laws, restrictions or regulations (collectively the “Export Laws”).&#xA;In addition, if the Software is identified as an export controlled&#xA;item under the Export Laws, you represent and warrant that you&#xA;are not a citizen of, or located within, an embargoed or otherwise&#xA;restricted nation  and that you are not otherwise prohibited&#xA;under the Export Laws from receiving the Software. All rights&#xA;to use the Software are granted on condition that such rights&#xA;are forfeited if you fail to comply with the terms of this agreement.&#xA;10. Governing Law.&#xA;If you are a consumer who uses the Software for only personal&#xA;non-business purposes, then this agreement will be governed by&#xA;the laws of the state in which you purchased the license to use&#xA;the Software. If you are not such a consumer, this agreement&#xA;will be governed by and construed in accordance with the substantive&#xA;laws in force in SWITZERLAND. The commercial court of the canton&#xA;of Aargau shall have non-exclusive jurisdiction over all disputes&#xA;relating to this agreement. This agreement will not be governed&#xA;by the conflict of law rules of any jurisdiction or the United&#xA;Nations Convention on Contracts for the International Sale of&#xA;Goods, the application of which is expressly excluded.&#xA;11. General Provisions.&#xA;If any part of this agreement is found void and unenforceable,&#xA;it will not affect the validity of the balance of this agreement,&#xA;which will remain valid and enforceable according to its terms&#xA;This agreement may only be modified in writing, signed by an&#xA;authorized officer of cleonproject.deliverables.architecture. This is the entire agreement&#xA;between cleonproject.deliverables.architecture and you relating to the Software and it supersedes&#xA;any prior representations, discussions, undertakings, communications&#xA;or advertising relating to the Software.&#xA;12. Compliance with Licenses.&#xA;If you are a business, company, or organization, you agree that,&#xA;no more than once every 12 months, cleonproject.deliverables.architecture or its authorized&#xA;representative shall, upon 10 days’ prior notice to you, have&#xA;the right to inspect your records, systems, and facilities to&#xA;verify that your use of any and all cleonproject.deliverables.architecture software is in&#xA;conformity with your valid licenses from cleonproject.deliverables.architecture. If a verification&#xA;discloses that your use is not in conformity with a valid license,&#xA;you shall immediately obtain valid licenses to bring your use&#xA;into conformity.&#xA;13. Internet Connectivity and Privacy.&#xA;13.1 Automatic Connections to the Internet.&#xA;The Software may cause your Computer to automatically connect&#xA;to the Internet and to communicate with an cleonproject.deliverables.architecture website&#xA;for purposes that may include providing you with additional information,&#xA;features and functionality. The following provisions apply to&#xA;all automatic Internet connections by the Software:&#xA;13.1.1 When the Software automatically connects to the Internet,&#xA;an Internet protocol address (“IP Address”) that is associated&#xA;with your current Internet connection is sent to an cleonproject.deliverables.architecture&#xA;website;&#xA;13.1.2 When the Software automatically connects to the Internet,&#xA;no personally identifiable information is sent except to the&#xA;extent that IP Addresses may be considered personally identifiable&#xA;in some jurisdictions; and&#xA;13.1.3 Whenever the Software makes an Internet connection and&#xA;communicates with an cleonproject.deliverables.architecture website, unless you are provided&#xA;with separate terms of use at that time, the cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.com&#xA;Terms of Use (http://www.cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.com) shall apply. Please&#xA;note that the cleonproject.deliverables.architecture Privacy Policy allows tracking of website&#xA;visits and it addresses in detail the topic of tracking and use&#xA;of cookies, web beacons and similar devices.&#xA;13.1.4 The Software may transmit your serial number and your&#xA;e-mail address you used to register your license to cleonproject.deliverables.architecture&#xA;and in doing so may prevent uses of the Software that are not&#xA;permitted.&#xA;13.2 Updating. The Software may cause your Computer to automatically&#xA;connect to the Internet to check for Updates that are available&#xA;for automatic download to your Computer and to let cleonproject.deliverables.architecture&#xA;know the Software is successfully installed. Please consult the&#xA;Documentation for information about changing default update settings.&#xA;13.4 Use of cleonproject.deliverables.architecture Online Services. The Software may use&#xA;your Computer to automatically connect to the Internet to facilitate&#xA;your access to content and services that are provided to you&#xA;by cleonproject.deliverables.architecture. Your Software may automatically update downloadable&#xA;materials from these services so as to provide immediate availability&#xA;of these services even when you are offline. Please consult the&#xA;Documentation for information about changing default update settings.&#xA;13.5 Digital Certificates. The Software uses digital certificates&#xA;to help you identify downloaded files (e.g., applications and&#xA;content) and the publishers of those files. Your Computer may&#xA;connect to the Internet at the time of validation of a digital&#xA;certificate.&#xA;14. Specific Provisions and Exceptions.&#xA;This section sets forth specific provisions related to certain&#xA;products and components of the Software as well as limited exceptions&#xA;to the above terms and conditions. To the extent that any provision&#xA;in this section is in conflict with any other term or condition&#xA;in this agreement, this section will supersede such other term&#xA;or condition.&#xA;14.1 No Prejudice, European Union Provisions.&#xA;14.1.1 This agreement will not prejudice the statutory rights&#xA;of any party, including those dealing as consumers. For example,&#xA;for consumers in New Zealand who obtain the Software for personal,&#xA;domestic or household use (not business purposes), this agreement&#xA;is subject to the Consumer Guarantees Act.&#xA;14.1.2 If you obtained the Software in the European Union (EU),&#xA;you usually reside in the EU and you are a consumer (that is&#xA;you use the Software for personal, non-business related purposes),&#xA;then Section 6 does not apply to your purchase and use of the&#xA;Software. Instead, cleonproject.deliverables.architecture warrants for a period of 2 years&#xA;from purchase that the Software provides the functionalities&#xA;set forth in the Documentation (the “agreed upon functionalities”)&#xA;when used on the recommended hardware configuration. Non-substantial&#xA;variation from the agreed upon functionalities will not establish&#xA;any warranty rights. THIS WARRANTY DOES NOT APPLY TO SOFTWARE&#xA;THAT YOU REQUEST TO USE ON A PRE-RELEASE, TRYOUT, STARTER, PRODUCT&#xA;SAMPLER BASIS, OR TO FONT SOFTWARE CONVERTED INTO OTHER FORMATS&#xA;OR TO THE EXTENT THE SOFTWARE FAILS TO PERFORM BECAUSE IT HAS&#xA;BEEN ALTERED BY YOU. To make a warranty claim, you must notify&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.architecture during this 2 year period, providing details of proof&#xA;of purchase of the Software. cleonproject.deliverables.architecture will verify with you&#xA;whether there is a defect in the Software or advise you that&#xA;the error arises because you have not installed the Software&#xA;correctly (in which case, cleonproject.deliverables.architecture shall assist you). If there&#xA;is a defect in the Software, you may request from cleonproject.deliverables.architecture&#xA;either a refund or a repaired/replacement copy of the Software.&#xA;Requests must be accompanied by proof of purchase. In the event&#xA;your warranty details are substantiated, cleonproject.deliverables.architecture will meet&#xA;your request for repaired/replacement Software, unless it is&#xA;not reasonable for cleonproject.deliverables.architecture to do so, in which case cleonproject.deliverables.architecture&#xA;will provide you with a refund. For warranty assistance, please&#xA;contact cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.&#xA;Please note that the provisions of Section 8 (Limitation of Liability)&#xA;will continue to apply to any damages claims you make in respect&#xA;of your use of the Software. Nonetheless, cleonproject.deliverables.architecture shall be&#xA;liable for direct losses that are reasonably foreseeable in the&#xA;event of a breach by cleonproject.deliverables.architecture of this agreement. You are advised&#xA;to take all reasonable measures to avoid and reduce damages,&#xA;in particular by making back-up copies of the Software and your&#xA;computer data.&#xA;This agreement, and in particular, this Section 14.1.2, is intended&#xA;to describe your rights (including your statutory rights) in&#xA;the event there should be problems with your use of the Software.&#xA;If your statutory rights should be greater than this description,&#xA;your statutory rights shall apply.&#xA;14.2 Pre-release Software Additional Terms. If the Software is&#xA;pre-commercial release or beta software (“Pre-release Software”),&#xA;then this section applies. The Pre-release Software is a pre-release&#xA;version, does not represent final product from cleonproject.deliverables.architecture, and&#xA;may contain bugs, errors and other problems that could cause&#xA;system or other failures and data loss. cleonproject.deliverables.architecture may never&#xA;commercially release the Pre-release Software. If you received&#xA;the Pre-release Software pursuant to a separate written agreement&#xA;your use of the Software is also governed by such agreement.&#xA;You will return or destroy all copies of Pre-release Software&#xA;upon request by cleonproject.deliverables.architecture or upon cleonproject.deliverables.architecture’s commercial&#xA;release of such Software. YOUR USE OF PRE-RELEASE SOFTWARE IS&#xA;AT YOUR OWN RISK. SEE SECTIONS 7 AND 8 FOR WARRANTY DISCLAIMERS&#xA;AND LIABILITY LIMITATIONS WHICH GOVERN PRE-RELEASE SOFTWARE.&#xA;If you have any questions regarding this agreement or if you&#xA;wish to request any information from cleonproject.deliverables.architecture please use the&#xA;address and contact information included with this product to&#xA;contact cleonproject.deliverables.architecture.&#xA;cleonproject.deliverables.architecture is a registered trademark of cleonproject.deliverables.architecture in the Switzerland&#xA;and/or other countries. All other trademarks are the property&#xA;of their respective owners.
        </license>
      </licenses>
      <copyright uri='http://www.zwyssig.info/copyright' url='http://www.zwyssig.info/copyright'>
        Zwyssig Informatik GmbH
      </copyright>
    </unit>
  </units>
</repository>
